[Adapted from Wanzhi's
"Perfect and Casual"]
[Perfect and Casual]
[Episode 15]
Get in the car.
I will drive you there.
Won't you be late for class?
If you get in the car now,
we won't be late.
Mr Zhang.
What to do?
There's a traffic jam.
There's indeed been an accident ahead.
This is not part of my plan.
We will be late for work.
Or I can get off
and walk down the congested street.
Then I'll take a taxi.
That's a good idea.
Well, watch your step when you get off.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Someone is behind.
Ignore him.
Motorcycle robbery
often use these tactics.
It's dangerous.
Yun Shu.
It's me.
-Lawyer Meng?
-Mr Zhang.
Mr Zhang.
Stuck in the jam?
Yun Shu.
You'll lose your full
attendance bonus this month
if you're still here.
Mr Zhang.
I'm getting off.
Mr Zhang, hey.
Wait a minute.
How can you?
Why did you step on the gas?
Look, your car crashed into my car.
Sorry.
Lawyer Meng?
I just got into an accident.
As my attorney,
I now demand that you
deal with this.
Don't you have insurance?
Besides, it's not office hours.
I won't take it.
According to our contract,
you need to provide 24/7 services.
Do you need me
to show you the terms?
What are you doing?
Yun Shu, get on.
You can ride a motorcycle?
Is there anything I can't do?
Go on.
Hold on.
Sir.
It's alright.
Nothing serious.
If you call me for such
trivial matters again,
I'll raise my agency fee.
Do I care?
Next year's consultant
may not be you.
Did you know?
I heard from Mei
that she saw Lu Yu holding Yun Lan
and twirling in the office.
By the way, was that Lu Yu who we saw
at the entrance last time?
It should be.
But I think
there was something between them.
That's why
Lu Yu is now an intern in our company.
And he is Yun Lan's assistant.
So clever.
Yun Lan has some brilliant tricks.
She just played
a cat-and-mouse game.
Well,
we really need to study from her.
Learn such tricks.
I think you should learn more than that.
Stop!
You should work harder
instead of gossiping.
Nevertheless,
I can also understand both of you.
After all, any woman would
be jealous and resentful.
Because Yun Lan is better than you.
You should indeed learn from her
in the aspects of self-motivation
and dedication.
She doesn't waste time
gossiping about others.
I'm indeed pursuing her.
I'm sincere about it.
It's not because of tricks
like cat-and-mouse
as you said.
Who said I didn't use tricks?
Yun Lan.
If not,
how could I have become
Lu Yu's girlfriend?
Why are you still here?
Where's our privacy?
Sorry, Miss Yun.
Sorry!
It doesn't matter.
I would like to thank you
for giving me the courage.
My dear,
you have accepted me.
Why?
Are you regretting it?
No, of course not.
Yes, I have received it.
I'm so sorry to have
troubled you this time.
Okay.
No problem.
Yun Shu.
By the way.
If you are free,
I would like to take my client with me.
Okay.
Then, see you tonight.
Yun Shu,
I have something to tell you.
I made a decision
without consulting you.
Do you mind?
Mr Meng.
Are you going to sack me?
Why would I?
You are the lucky star of our company.
Why would I fire you?
You scared me.
This is the latest info on Huo Qi.
My cousin's?
Last time you told me that you
were cheated by your cousin,
I asked someone
to look into him in secret.
But I didn't tell you this matter
until I found his whereabouts recently.
Do you
think that I'm being nosey?
No, I don't.
That's good
I was afraid you would be angry.
No.
Mr Meng.
Thank you.
Are you free this evening?
I'm meeting the person
in charge of the investigation.
You can go with me
if you are free tonight,
as you have more
information than I have.
This can help us to find the
person we have been looking for.
Okay.
Just like what she said just now.
For this house, she was cheated out of
two million yuan or so by her cousin.
And I have also
prepared some materials today,
including
the personal information of her cousin,
the latest records of his communication
and the invoice for purchasing
the house at that time.
Okay. I have a rough idea of the case.
I will contact you
if there is any update.
Okay.
Thank you for your hard work, Cui.
-Thanks.
-Bye.
Mr Meng.
Thank you very much for today.
You've thanked me enough.
No need to be so polite.
Regarding this matter,
I will have to thank you
over and over.
Because it's really important for me
to find my cousin.
I know.
I can understand your feeling.
Because
I had a similar experience before.
I was deceived by a person I trusted.
Then?
Then, later on, I began studying law.
I told myself
to believe in the evidence
instead of believing in myself blindly.
Mr Zhang,
why are you still up?
You are back.
Have you had dinner yet?
I left some dishes for
you in the refrigerator.
I had dinner.
You came back so late.
Worked overtime again?
No,
I went along with Lawyer Meng
to meet a person.
Lawyer Meng?
Lawyer Meng was on purpose.
The Labour Law has clearly defined
the working hours per day
shall not be more than eight hours
Mr Zhang.
It was Lawyer Meng who helped me
and went with me to meet the person.
He...
accompanied you?
Who did you meet?
Lawyer Meng found an investigator
to look into my cousin's affairs.
I went to meet him
to exchange news and information.
Yun Shu.
If you want to find your cousin
in a fastest manner,
the most effective and quickest way is
to report him to the
public security bureau,
rather than try to solve it
on your own.
I really don't want to send my cousin
to the public security bureau.
But you can't deny
this is the most effective way.
Mr Zhang,
the guy Mr Meng found
is also efficient.
Maybe there will be news in a few days.
He just tried to get close to you
on purpose.
Get close to me?
Why?
It doesn't matter.
I just don't want you
to be disappointed.
Mr Zhang.
Lawyer Meng is quite reliable.
He didn't tell me the truth
before he got the result
because he was worried
I'd get disappointed.
So what's the result?
Here.
This is information about my cousin.
[You have changed yourself
so much for Wu Suo Wei,]
[and have done so much for him.]
[If you are still unhappy,]
[I, Nan Tian,]
[will not be happy either.]
Cheers!
I could tell,
you got drunk on purpose
that time when you had a drink abroad.
Those few days were the worst
during my time abroad.
They were more difficult than
when I first arrived.
To live a splendid life
in the rush of reality
is what we need to do most.
What nonsense are you talking about?
It's an old Chinese saying.
Your worst days
are also my happiest days.
Happy?
Yeah.
If you hadn't had the bad luck,
we wouldn't have been
acquainted with each other.
Maybe it is.
Cheers!
From today on,
I will help Yun Shu
to find her cousin.
You don't worry about it.
Don't forget,
it was you who let Yun Shu
ask me to help her look
into the affairs of Huo Qi.
It seems that I haven't
made it clear enough.
So, I'm now giving you a
formal notice, Mr Meng.
You need not concern yourself
with this matter.
Sorry.
This matter is now a personal one.
You have no right to decide it.
Then, I guess I need to remind you
to not cross the line.
Cross the line?
Whose? Yours?
Or Yun Shu's?
It is the line between you and me.
You needn't worry about that.
I will establish a new
relationship with Yun Shu
after your contract with her ends.
How dare you!
Why don't I dare?
The relationship between you and Yun Shu
only stands when in front of your grandpa.
So?
Why can't I help Yun Shu
in private?
Let me take care of Huo Qi's matter.
As a lawyer, I should
help my client solve the problem.
What did you say just now?
Investigation?
Trace?
Didn't you hear anything I said?
Were you ever in a suspense play before?
Share your experience with me.
Suspense play?
No, I didn't.
Aren't you a popular actor?
Our company once
tried to recommend me a suspense play,
but the story was too complicated.
I didn't understand it,
so I turned it down.
I have really overestimated you.
Back to the point.
Why are you doing an investigation?
I'm just trying to help
Yun Shu find her cousin.
Cousin?
It is the cousin who acted as a
matchmaker
and deceived Yun Shu into buying a house?.
Watch your wording.
Matchmaker?
Isn't he a matchmaker?
Without him, could both of you
have gotten married?
Are we not talking about the point?
Go ahead with your story.
According to some information
of Huo Qi provided by Meng Ran,
in the past ten days,
Huo Qi often visited a branch of
Yikang Pharmacy
on Juxian Road to shop.
He went there every three days
and the amount spent each time
was almost the same.
Therefore, according to my analysis,
Huo Qi is most likely injured.
Oh, Nian Nian,
you are so awesome!
You're really a modern-day
Sherlock Holmes!
Stop!
Today happens to be the day
for changing dressings.
I'm going to stake out
and catch Huo Qi.
And then?
And then...
I will persuade him to turn himself in.
I thought Yun Shu didn't want
to involve the police.
Now that he has broken the law,
he should be punished by the law.
This is also my principle.
As a legal worker,
I support you.
But
the law is no more than human nature!
It seems to make some sense.
Put it this way.
This depends on
what you deem more important,
Yun Shu or your principle?
By the way.
Tell you a piece of happy news!
I'm now your brother-in-law.
An elder?
At your age,
you've been considered
an old artist long ago.
I have been officially upgraded to
Yun Lan's boyfriend.
Yun Lan's boyfriend?
It's true.
Sure enough, Yun Lan
only looks smart.
What are you saying?
Dong Ge, go and eat.
The dishes today are really yummy.
Alright. I'll go and eat then.
Bye.
Could you please
order less dishes next time?
Since I always sponge off your lunch,
I feel kind of bad about it.
Only twin sets
get a discount.
If you feel embarrassed,
you can return the hospitality.
Okay. Then I will treat you next time.
I know a restaurant with...
Gu Xiao?
You know him?
Mum, this is Gu Xiao.
How are you feeling today?
Take good care of yourself.
You needn't worry about
other things.
You're really something.
You have the aunty under control.
You can come here at any time.
Well, being lovable is also a gift,
so I can't help it.
I met Gu Xiao in the hospital yesterday.
He has a relative who is
going to have surgery.
So he has been busy with this matter.
Relative?
Do you know what relative?
Just a relative.
Why would I ask about that?
No, I mean...
Oh no,
I'm going to be late.
Remember to close the door
when you leave.
Hey, what's the hurry?
Didn't you make an appointment at 11:30?
I want to go Gu Xiao's company
in advance
to give him a surprise.
I will drive you there.
I...
I happen to be going that way.
Really?
Yes.
[Metro, Railway station]
Why is it so jammed?
Maybe you'd better not go.
Give up eating for fear of choking?
Miss the appointment
due to a traffic jam?
Are you crazy?
Yeah.
If I wasn't crazy,
would I send you to your date?
If Gu Xiao really wanted
to have a date with you,
he should pick you up.
I'm not that hypocritical.
Forget about it. I'd walk there.
Gu Xiao's company is just ahead.
Sir, drop me off here.
But what's the rush?
Your makeup will run.
Sir, drop me here.
How much?
I'll scan the QR code.
Yi Yi, wait!
Hurry up!
-Yi Yi.
-What's the matter?
Your hair is a mess.
Why not look at yourself in the mirror?
Flawless!
Yi Yi.
Now what?
Can I have a word with you?
Go ahead.
Let me go first.
Gu Xiao will see us.
Um...
Go ahead.
I... Um...
We broke up a long time ago,
but there is always a
place for you in my heart
I don't want to...
I don't want to make you sad.
I...
I'm not sad.
Actually I'm living a happy life now.
Can you just let me go?
Don't let Gu Xiao see us!
Hurry up!
No, I mean...
Just in case.
What if?
What if you get hurt again?
No way.
I won't let you go.
Lin Nuo.
If you dare,
I will slap you, believe it or not?
Please, don't do that!
Hey.
Don't go to meet him today.
Lin Nuo,
I'm going to lose my temper.
If you continue to behave like
this, we can't even be friends.
Finally.
Excuse me?
I said you can finally go.
I was just kidding.
What's wrong with you today?
Yi Yi.
Why are you here?
Didn't we arrange to meet
at the restaurant?
I wanted to surprise you!
-What do you think of my dress?
-Gu Xiao.
Very nice!
I left my mobile phone in your pocket.
Mobile phone.
Hello, I'm Gu Xiao's girlfriend.
I'm sorry, but
I need to talk to her.
Yi Yi.
You already knew about this, right?
I...
So you came here
to laugh at me, didn't you?
Yi Yi, that's not true.
Just leave me alone.
[Yun Shu, I'm terribly sorry.]
[I was held up by something just now.]
[I will be home at eight.]
[No problem, Mr Zhang.]
Yun Shu.
Could you do me a favour?
Today I'm going to meet
a very important guest.
Would you please
help me fix up a place for the meeting?
Here is the address.
You need to grab something first
before you go to the restaurant.
The restaurant manager will help you.
Huachu House, Flaubert Western Restaurant.
What do you mean by important guests?
Those vital to the
development of our law firm.
Okay.
I'll see it done.
Hello.
[Hello.]
[Hello, Mr Zhang.]
[Your cake is ready.]
[Do you need delivery?]
Yes, please deliver it.
[Will do.]
-I will send you the address later.
-[Okay.]
Please be sure to arrive before 8:00 p.m.
[Got it.]
Okay. Thanks.
Hello.
Miss Yun Shu, right?
Yes.
Leave it to me.
Okay.
Here you go.
It looks expensive.
Okay, please rest assured.
Mr Meng has a message for you.
Wait here.
He will be here soon.
Okay.
Also, Mr Meng has booked
the whole restaurant
so we cleared the place.
Only one attendant will be left.
After a while, I will leave.
If there is any problem,
you can turn to him.
Thank you.
Okay.
Then please follow me.
-Okay.
-This way.
Huo Qi.
Hello, Sis.
Tonight let's have dinner together.
But tonight...
Mr Zhang will wait for me at home.
You guys enjoy.
I have a meeting to attend later.
I‘ll hang up.
Okay.
By the way,
I have been busy these days.
I'll give you your birthday
present in a few days.
Thank you, Sis.
Bye.
[Mr Zhang, sorry! I'm still working.
I'll be home  abit late]
Huo Qi.
Stop!
[Police]
Since young,
aside from my sister,
he has been the closest person to me.
I just don't want him
to be ruined because of this.
You're here, Mr Meng.
Sorry, Yun Shu.
I was held up by something.
You had to wait.
It's okay.
I have delivered the item
to the restaurant.
I also decorated the place.
Looks good.
Yun Shu.
What do you say?
It's nice.
Cosy and low-key.
I'm glad you like it.
If there's nothing else,
I'm going to go.
♫ Why are two persons from
different worlds intertwined? ♫
♫ What kind of endings
will the different melody scores bring ♫
♫ Trying to find the secret of the fall ♫
♫ Who can differentiate
between reality and dream? ♫
♫ Listening to your footsteps,
getting closer ♫
♫ That is love, slowly,
gradually fermenting ♫
♫ Unsure how to express it,
choosing to be bold ♫
♫ This time, it will be
the most wonderful decision ♫
Happy birthday, Yun Shu.
[Yun Shu, happy birthday]
[Mr Zhang.]
[Sorry!]
[I'm still working.
I'll be home a bit late.]
Yun Shu.
I like you.
Mr Meng.
I'm married to Mr Zhang.
I know.
You and Mr Zhang have a
contractual marriage lasting one year.
But Yun Shu,
you shouldn't be bound by it.
You're entitled to be loved.
You're entitled to choose who to love.
But...
Zhang Si Nian knows everything.
Before I confessed my love to you,
I told him everything.
Then...
What did Mr Zhang say?
What did he say?
It doesn't matter.
No.
It is important to me.
Why?
Because I like him.
Yun Shu.
During human interaction,
we develop different affections
like family ties,
friendship,
love
or
even gratitude.
Gratitude?
When you were at your worst,
you met Zhang Si Nian.
He helped you get out of trouble
and overcome difficulties.
Then,
you held a wedding
and have been together since.
It's not surprising you have
developed feelings toward him.
But you need to know,
this feeling
is not necessarily love.
Then, Mr Meng.
What is love?
There is no exact answer.
But I know
your affection towards him
is anything but love.
I trust my own feelings more.
Yun Shu.
I truly
hope you can think about it
seriously.
You and Zhang Si Nian.
What exactly is your relationship?
I really have to go.
Then let me see you off.
It's okay.
Bye.
Sir.
Excuse me, can you drive a little faster?
I'm really in a rush.
Girl, this is a taxi,
not a plane.
Yun Shu.
Mr Meng?
Sorry.
I was too selfish just now
and didn't consider your feelings.
Love.
There has never been a
standard answer to that question.
Yun Shu,
I respect your feelings.
But meanwhile,
I also respect my own feelings.
Every year,
how many times will you
replace your phone?
Each year, I...
Professor Zhang.
Where are you going?
I'm going to pick up my wife.
You've forgotten your phone.
Thank you.
Go up.