[Adapted from Wanzhi's
"Perfect and Casual"]
[Perfect and Casual]
[Episode 9]
Yun Shu.
Mr Zhang.
You can sign your name.
Where shall I sign my name?
OK, I'm done.
What did you sign?
My name.
Are you kidding me?
[Party B signature]
Mr Zhang, I'm sorry.
I got it wrong.
Sorry, Mr Zhang. I'll correct that.
Forget it
I'll reprint a new one
I was thinking about
something else just now.
[Oh, my gosh.]
[Yun Shu.]
[What are you doing?]
[My Understanding of Mathematics]
Yun Shu.
Mr Zhang.
Did you do the exercises
I bought for you last time?
Yes, I did. I've done it.
Show me.
Okay.
They are just half done,
But,
a good beginning
is half the battle won.
Get dressed.
We're going to school.
What?
Why are we going to school?
Get off the car.
Mr Zhang,
maybe I shouldn't
attend the class today.
Looks like you haven't mastered
Definition of Dynamic Series.
I happen to have this class today,
so you can sit in.
Sit in?
Mr Zhang.
Morning, Mr Zhang.
Morning.
Get off the car.
Mr Zhang,
how about telling me the classroom number?
I'll go myself
Room 319.
Okay.
Hello.
Is the seat taken?
Yes.
Okay.
Hello, the seat isn't taken, right?
No.
You have a special knapsack.
Really?
The desk is for students' studying
rather than your showing
off your knapsack.
Yun Shu.
Come here.
It's fine.
What the heck?
I'll first introduce the
two types of relative number.
All right,
that's all for today.
Class is over.
See you, students.
Thanks, Sir.
Mr Zhang is really a timer.
As soon as he stops,
the bell rings.
Yun Shu.
-What's the relationship between them?
-No idea.
You have to concentrate in class.
Don't just stare into space.
OK, I got it.
Clean the blackboard.
I want that one.
Come with me.
Mr Zhang.
Thanks.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Spinach is rich in Vitamin A,
C1, B1 and B2.
It is one of the major suppliers for
brain cells to metabolize wastes.
But,
I really don't like spinach.
And
I think I have enough brain cells.
Alright.
Tell me the major contents
of the two classes you had in the morning.
Alright, I'll eat them up
I'll eat them right now.
You also need to have more fish.
Mr Zhang,
I think my brain has long
ceased to develop.
Not really.
Have some more.
Egg
can promote your memory.
Rice.
Okay.
I mean your face.
What's wrong with my face?
I mean the rice.
I mean that the rice
was on your face.
You mean Mr Zhang
took you to attend his class
and he took off the rice on your face.
Yun Shu.
You smell strange?
What?
I had a shower before
I went out this morning.
Is it the sweat smell?
I ran in school today.
Mr Zhang must smell it.
It's a smell of
falling in love.
You freaked me out.
Yi Yi.
And I feel like
that I really fell in love with Mr Zhang.
Great.
Whatever, if you like a man,
you should take the initiative.
But we're contractual relationship.
Maybe he doesn't
like me.
Look at you, little fool.
Mr Zhang married you.
He gave you a house.
Also, he took you to his
class and fed you publicly.
He definitely loves you.
What more do you want?
Well, what if he just
fulfil his performance?
Who cares?
If you try,
the contractual relationship
can turn to be a real love.
What should I do then?
First,
you should give him a hint that
you're in a relationship now.
And then you can give
him some love signals.
Giving him the eye.
And finally,
you can take action.
Just show your feelings
to Mr Zhang directly.
So.
He'll know your mind.
OK, I got it.
You...
You've known that?
You paid attention
to my lecture yesterday,
so the accuracy of this testing paper
rose by 30 percent.
Why have you been
staring at me recently?
I... I... I haven't.
Do you wanna
ask me any questions?
Well, Mr Zhang, I have something for you.
Wait a second, I'm going to get it.
Pyjamas.
Coloured?
I show the wrong one.
It's not yours.
This one is yours.
They both look the same.
Because they're sweetheart outfits.
The sweetheart outfit of
the store are on sale today.
So I bought them.
Egyptian Cotton.
It feels nice
I'll take this gift.
Anyway.
The income of financing
is your cost of daily living.
In the future,
you can spend more money on yourself.
OK, I got it.
It's late today.
Go to the bed and have a rest.
Good night.
Many shop assistants can judge
what kind of person the customer is.
So an excellent shop
assistant should be equipped
with this important working technique.
If we can digitalize our
intuitive judgment,
we can get our desired answer
by computing.
First step,
we can set
the prior probability
through our experience.
Mr Zhang is really handsome.
He doesn't only look good,
but also knowledgeable.
Really?
Oh, give me break.
Don't be his fangirls.
Bullshit.
It's useless for him to be knowledgeable.
He's just teaching math.
So what?
Math is the cornerstone
of human development.
Do you know that?
Cornerstone?
It's just a stepping-stone.
You know nothing.
Shallow people like you
will have a gloomy future.
I have a gloomy future?
Do you know how much money I
can earn through playing games?
I'm not interested in it.
It's time for class now.
If you have any question,
you can raise the question
so that we can have a discussion.
Since Mr Zhang let us to discuss it.
I'd like to ask you something.
Mr Zhang,
Those subjects we have to learn such as
mathematical analysis,
complex function,
reliability mathematics and et cetera
won't be useful in life
once we graduate.
What's the point?
Can we get a job with it?
How much will we earn?
If I team with my
classmates to play games,
we can earn much more money.
It seems that you're a curious student.
You raised three questions just now.
Well, what is Math?
Math lays the rational
foundation for people
to know the world.
Though many irrational
behaviours abound
in the world,
people always hope they can
picture these phenomena in a rational way.
For example,
in terms of statistics,
we have some mental effects
like the Matthew Effect,
Break Pane Law,
Marshmallow Effect and so on.
Besides,
in anthropology,
there are also
the Crowd Theory
and the Wisdom of Crowds.
Hold on, Mr Zhang.
I can't understand what you said just now.
Can you put it plainly?
You play games, right?
Computer games?
Yeah.
In the middle of last century,
Turing and von Neumann
by virtue of their solid
mathematical knowledge,
created the structural pattern
of modern computer,
leading people
into the Information Age.
No offence.
If there is no math,
you and your team members
can only play games
using an abacus.
I don't play games,
but I know
in the professional e-sports scene,
the key to win the game
is still math.
Am I right?
I always believe that
we didn't choose math
but math chose us.
Oh, my god. He's amazing.
Follow up!
He convinced others with his
high IQ. He's really excellent.
Can you be more reserved, Gao Zhi Yi?
Mr Zhang is Yun Shu's husband now.
I'm just reflecting Yun Shu's
inner feelings.
Right, Yun Shu?
Come on.
Are you really angry?
Of course not. Why would I be?
I'm just thinking.
The gap between Mr Zhang and I
is so big.
Kind of.
But it's not a big deal.
You just need to be braver.
I've told you that you
need to show your feelings.
Give him some signals. Did you do that?
Yes.
You did?
What did you do?
I bought him a new lounge wear
using the interest from my investment.
And they're his-and-hers.
Did he take it?
Yes.
Did he say anything?
He said...
"Not bad."
That's it.
What?
You and Mr Zhang are doing it for real.
We have to take further action.
Be more initiative.
You have to make Mr
Zhang feel your presence.
You have to overwhelm him
with your great love.
Who is it? Who hit me?
Do you know how to play basketball?
You didn't see people here?
Sorry. My bad.
Are you OK?
Oh, come on. What department are you in?
Don't be so rude to him.
I'm fine.
Thanks.
Are you really okay?
Let's go to have a check at the hospital.
Oh, come on. You can have a try.
Let me hit you.
You...
I'm really OK. No biggie.
What department are you in?
I've never seen you before.
I've long graduated.
I just came here to run an errand
and just dropped by to play basketball
I'm Gu Xiao.
I'm Gao Zhi Yi.
Can I have your WeChat?
OK.
WeChat me if you have any problem.
Alright, I'll treat you
to dinner some day.
Let's continue.
I'll pick your eyes up from the ground
and put them back,
in case you became blind.
Look. Just as I said.
It's really easy for a
woman to chase after a man.
Yi Yi, wipe your mouth.
I can see your drool.
Oh, come on.
You have to make it clear to me.
What's going on with your divorce?
Mum!
This is my workplace.
I'll tell you everything at home, OK?
No way.
Don't call me mum.
Shame on you.
If you're divorced,
what will you do in the future?
Once you get divorced,
it's not easy for you to
remarry someone else.
If you really dare to get divorced,
I'll cut ties with you.
Mum!
Don't talk nonsense.
Miss Shen.
I need you to help me
to adjust the working
schedule for next week.
OK, Professor Zhang.
Hello,
you're Lan Lan's superior, right?
Hello.
Alright, listen.
Can you be the judge?
Shen Lan...
Mum.
Just stop.
Miss Shen is an outstanding person.
She's great at logical thinking
or emotional control.
Come on, Mum, let's leave.
Look at you.
Do you know that gossip is dreadful?
You've really let me down.
Alright, I'll go.
Professor Zhang,
can I sit here?
Be my guest.
I want to thank you for
what you did for me today.
No worries.
I just told her what I saw.
By the way, Miss Shen,
does a divorce really affect
the modern women vastly?
Hard to say.
But it will exert some
impact more or less.
People won't care too much
about what happened between a couple.
I won't be like Xiang Lin's wife,
so I won't explain everything to everyone.
Therefore,
people will guess
what happened,
and over time,
what the truth is
no longer matters.
Maybe it's just as your mum said just now.
Rumour is dreadful.
Yes.
[Yun Shu.]
[You don't have to prepare dinner for me.]
[I'm staying late for work.]
[Gender Relations in
China's Current Social Formation ]
What are you doing?
Mr Zhang.
I just finished doing laundry.
I folded your clothes
and put them into your wardrobe.
Mr Zhang,
you still read fairy tales?
That's very kind of you.
You should just take care
of yourself in the future
I can take care of my own affairs.
Okay.
I'll leave you then.
I'm done.
Mr Zhang,
the noodles I cooked
today doesn't taste good?
No.
Hold on, Mr Zhang.
After I finish my breakfast,
I'll be right with you.
Yun Shu.
From today on,
you don't have to attend my class.
You can study at home.
I'll answer your questions
when I'm home.
Mr Zhang,
did I do something wrong at school
and affected your teaching?
I was just thoughtless.
Our relationship
is likely to have some negative effects.
I indeed neglected
this aspect.
From today on,
we should avoid
showing up together in public,
especially in our shared
social environments
like the school.
Mr Zhang, I…
I'm going to be late.
I have to go.
Hello, is this express delivery?
Yeah.
Please tell me the express code.
5201314.
OK.
I love you all my life.
Don't go.
How did you know my phone number?
There's nothing I can't do.
Childish!
Do you know the difference
between you and a monkey?
One lives in caves.
And another one
lives in my heart.
Listen, you have to go to see a doctor.
What the hell do you want from me?
I want to you to be my girlfriend.
You really have a poor memory.
You should go to see a doctor with me.
You can't arouse my hormone.
How could it be?
I'm the prince charming
of 0.5 billion girls.
I'm not a girl.
I also don't dream.
No woman can refuse me
in this world.
Listen, you must think
you're living in a drama.
An idol, chick flick
where you are the successful alpha male.
Do you dare to bet with me?
Give me one month.
And I will step into your heart.
I can give you two months
and you won't even step
a foot inside my house.
Deal.
What?
I'll get in your house within two months.
Hold on.
Don't leave.
This is for you.
You have to take it.
It's a deal, Miss Yun.
Perfect.
Hello,
[Mrs Zhang,]
[when will you come for your photos?]
Photos?
[Yes, you said that]
[you would come to get the
photos on Wednesday afternoon.]
I'm so sorry. I forgot.
I'll go now.
I'll be right there.
Take it.
It's a bit heavy. Are you OK with it?
Never mind.
Take it easy.
-OK, thanks.
-Bye.
And then?
Then...
Nothing else.
What?
Nothing else?
It's so strange.
You were so good the day before.
You ate together and you gave him a gift.
Analyse the situation
from a Martian's perspective.
What Martian?
Women are from Venus
and men are from Mars.
Don't you know?
You really know nothing.
Oh, come on.
Listen to me.
You were good the day before.
How did things suddenly change
the next day?
I got it.
I…
Let me change my way of thinking.
I thought in a wrong way just now.
I really got it this time.
Last night, did Mr Zhang say
he'd be working late?
Yes.
So he came home late
and seemed exhausted?
Yeah.
That's it.
Men will feel down
or something like that
when they are tired from work.
So I guess Mr Zhang is just
too tired from work recently.
Little Lin,
it's the first time
you're giving sound opinion.
You deserve a praise.
What's this?
Hey, don't.
Wedding pictures.
Wow, they're so great.
I think Mr Zhang
is just not that into me.
Open your eyes.
Look at the way he looks at you.
Look.
What is it if not love?
What else can it be?
Is it love?
Be his sweetheart and cheer him up.
Make him forget his worries.
How do I do that?
You can be considerate towards him,
take care of him
or just show up in front of him suddenly
and give him a surprise.
A surprise?
Is that OK?
Of course.
Why don't you trust me?
Oh, I have to go to my class.
OK, study hard.
Bye.
There is something wrong.
Mr Zhang?
Thanks, Sir.
Miss Shen.
Yun Shu.
Sorry.
Why are you in a hurry?
What are you doing?
Yun Shu.
Mr Zhang.
What are you doing?
Hello, Professor Wu.
I was looking for you.
The academic affairs office
issued a new class table.
I want to discuss with you.
Mr Zhang.
Are you angry?
Yun Shu.
This morning I told you
not to go to school
and let more people know
about our relationship.
This will cause a lot
trouble for the future.
Mr Zhang,
why don't you want others
to know about us?
You look down on me?
How can you have this logic?
Mr Zhang,
you're better than me in all aspects.
I'm not good enough for you
though I signed a contract with you.
How did you come to this conclusion?
I didn't mean that.
So why are you afraid of the exposure
of our relationship?
Afraid?
First,
I'm not afraid to let others
know of our relationship.
Second,
I just don't want more people
know our relationship,
because once our deal is over
and more people know about us,
it is likely that your future
relationships and
marriage will be affected.
My future?
My relationships
and marriage?
Yun Shu.
This contract may influence your
reputation to some extent.
I was thoughtless.
But don't worry.
I'll draft a supplemental agreement.
So if your future boyfriend
and husband misunderstands,
I'll explain everything to them.
Mr Zhang.
So all along,
you just thought of me
as your Party B, right?
In this contract,
we are indeed Party A and Party B.
OK, I got it.
[Easter Egg Time]
Thanks.
Here, here. Come on
I'm here.
We're going to have a fancy lunch.
-Those dishes...
-Hey.
What's wrong?
You two jumped the queue.
What?
I said you jumped the queue
so you should go to the end of the line.
Miss, what's the big deal?
Don't make a fuss.
Just shut it.
Yeah.
Yes, shut it.
Mr Zhang.
It's peak lunch hour.
They are 12 people queuing up.
If each one takes
two and a half minutes to order,
and you passed 11 people,
that means
you saved 27 and a half minutes.
You two occupied
the time of the other 11 students,
five minutes per person.
Do you still think it's not a big deal?
Sorry, Mr Zhang.
Thank you, Mr Zhang.
I want that one.
Come with me.