[Adapted from Wanzhi's
"Perfect and Casual"]
[Perfect and Casual]
[Episode 10]
If your future boyfriend
or husband
takes it the wrong way,
I'll explain everything
to them.
You just take me as your Party B, right?
In this contract,
we are Party A and Party B.
OK, I got it.
Yun Shu.
Are you up?
I want to talk with you.
Yun Shu.
[Mr Zhang, I'm moving out.
Here's your credit card.]
[My half of the utilities bill
is on the table. By: Yun Shu]
Yun Shu.
Yi Yi.
I can't understand you.
What's going on?
I let you give him signals
while you moved out.
I think Mr Zhang doesn't like me.
You told him your feelings?
No.
He told me that he didn't want
others to know about
our relationship.
It's obvious.
It's alright.
You don't have to move out.
You should just stay away from him.
I think my sister is right.
The psychological distance
begins with the physical distance.
And if I am bogged down in
that negative emotion deeper and deeper,
I will influence Mr Zhang.
Oh, save it.
Stop thinking of Mr Zhang.
You've totally lost your heart.
No.
I like Mr Zhang
and it's my own business.
Also, my father ever told me not
to make trouble for others.
But I keep making trouble
for Mr Zhang all the time.
Alright! Alright.
So what's your plan?
How about going back to my dormitory
to live in for several days?
Yi Yi,
I didn't eat breakfast.
I'm so hungry.
And I have no money now.
So take me to have something delicious.
Your father told you not to make
troubles for others, didn't he?
Let's go. Be my guest.
[Supermarket promoter urgently wanted.
Meals and lodging inclusive.]
It tastes good.
I have never eaten it before.
What's going on, Yun Shu?
[Supermarket promoter urgently wanted.
Meals and lodging inclusive.]
Come on.
There's always a way out.
[General Office]
Did you ever sell anything?
Before my graduation,
I sold some second-hand goods.
I did some part-time jobs
at malls when I was at college.
Is that OK?
The basic salary is 2,800 here.
There's also a commission
based on sales.
Are you OK with that?
Yes.
Do you offer dormitories?
Four people share one.
OK
No other requirements?
No.
Alright. Report for duty tomorrow.
Okay.
Thanks.
Can I move into the dormitory?
Yes, I'll arrange it for you.
Okay. Thank you.
Thanks.
[Till by oneself]
For your information,
if Party A feels
unsatisfied with the lawyer
assigned by Party B,
you can change the lawyer at any time.
But you shall illustrate your reasons.
This is a contract drafted by me.
Have a look first.
If there's anything I should
make an amendment,
you can let me know.
I feel like I'm taking
an exam while texting you.
I often think that
I didn't do well.
I've roughly glanced over it.
You don't have to amend anything.
I will see myself out.
I hope we have a pleasant cooperation.
Likewise.
[I'm From Outer Space]
Get in.
The bed is available.
You can sleep here.
Okay.
Hello,
I'm Yun Shu.
May I have your name?
I'm Mei.
Thanks.
Yun Shu
I'm done.
It's your turn.
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting for you.
You said you never watch things like this.
Were you lying?
Do you miss me?
Take them back.
I'm going home to sleep.
Take it.
Come on.
Yun Lan.
What do you want?
Let me give them back to you.
Your things are meaningless to me.
Just keep them for yourself.
Open the door.
What are you doing?
Enjoy...
Come, bro.
Cheers.
Come on.
Come on. Cheers.
Let's have a drink.
Come on.
I just
stopped her from watching the TV series
starring her favourite actor.
Then she kicked me out.
It's so unfair
I'm her boyfriend.
But she frowns on me.
And she always calls
those strangers on the TV
her husband.
It's so irritating.
Yes, it...
Come on, bro.
Come on, cheers.
Come on.
Cheers.
She made a mistake.
Don't take it personal.
Listen.
She'll get out and make an apology,
begging me to get back.
No way.
Listen, she won't.
You'll go too far.
Enough yet?
You go back first.
I'll have some drinks with them.
Bro.
Honey
I'm sorry.
My bad.
Don't be mad.
Sister-in-law.
Look... Don't get mad.
Tell you what,
I'll let them deliver your take-out
to your doorway.
Yes, sister-in-law.
Open the door.
Come on, forgive him.
You...
Thanks.
Bro, get in.
You're beautiful.
You have poor sleep.
I have to introduce a doctor to you.
Get out or shut up.
Hello, Senior.
I'm done working.
OK, see you later.
Look.
I made it.
It's harmful to drink Lemonade.
You had a good sleep last night?
Looks like my TV series
isn't completely useless.
Time to eat.
We can only sleep in on weekends.
Why did you get up so early?
It's the weekend.
Mei, go ahead.
I have to go.
You're really hilarious, Mr Zhang.
Show me the thermometer.
Mr Zhang is here.
Mr Zhang is in a good shape now.
You can talk with him.
Okay, thank you.
It's good to see that the
temperature went down.
Where is Yun Shu?
Did you fight?
Today, Yun Shu...
Grandpa.
Grandpa, I'm here.
She'll be a bit late.
Yes, I was held up by something.
However,
nothing is more important
than grandpa.
Yun Shu, you're really honey-lipped.
Look.
The blood pressure goes down immediately.
Grandpa, have a guess.
What have I got for you today?
What?
Durian.
Grandpa.
Ever since you told me that
you want to eat durian,
I bought the freshest one for you.
You're so sweet, Yun Shu.
Grandpa,
I'll cut one up for you to try.
Okay.
Alright.
The durian...
Si Nian, she's a girl.
It's hard for her to deal with the durian.
Go help her.
Let me do it.
Yun Shu.
Thank you for coming
here to visit grandpa.
Don't mention it. It's my duty.
I told you that I'll
follow the contract.
After all, grandpa gave you...
Never mind, I got a job.
I can support myself.
What kind of job?
A sale at a supermarket.
Huimin Supermarket,
not far away from home.
A sale at the supermarket?
Sale of beers.
I have a day off on Thursday.
Meals and accommodation included.
I have a basic salary
and commission from sales.
I think I understand now.
Understand what?
You're doing this to make yourself
more independent, aren't you?
I respect your choice.
But it's a hard way.
But since you've chosen it,
just stick to it. I believe you.
Go ahead.
Hello, director.
[Special offer]
Hello, hello.
Have a look at the beer promotions.
Buy a dozen and get a dozen free.
Girl, does the beer taste good?
Yes, have a try.
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
What are you doing?
Mr Zhang, why are you here?
I come to give you the exercises.
What's going on?
My sister is here.
I can't let her know
that I'm working here.
Don't look at her.
What to do then?
She's coming here.
What are you doing here?
Sis, why are you here?
To shop, of course.
Si Nian and I also want to buy something.
Si Nian said he wants to drink beer,
so I came here with him.
The beer was made from selected
wheat, imported with original packaging.
It's super rich.
Shall we buy a dozen?
I say, why do you dress so...
Here you are. They are for Yun Shu.
Thanks.
Sis.
Yun Shu, come with me.
What's going on, sis?
Zhang Si Nian is a nice guy.
Your sis...
She's gone. She didn't see the cracks.
Mr Zhang, thank you.
Don't mention it.
Because Article 5 in the contract
points out...
Yun Shu, the director is looking for you.
Go.
Mr Zhang,
thank you.
I can take care of myself.
Rest assured.
I have to go.
Come on! Come on!
I'm off now.
[Pocket file]
You begged to give you an opportunity.
And you promised me that you can do well.
So?
What did you do?
You offended our customer.
And you just ran away
after stepping on his feet.
Then you left for a while.
You didn't sell anything.
Sorry, director.
Please let me explain.
It really was an accident.
An accident?
You're my accident.
Listen, Yun Shu.
What do you want?
You're an undergraduate.
You work at our supermarket
for more experience of life?
No, director.
Listen to me,
I didn't mean that.
Go to the finance department
and get your salary settled.
This place
isn't big enough for you.
I'll get it done in 6 hours.
Please give me one more chance.
Though she's a casual labourer,
she shall be noticed in advance.
Or you'll disobey the
regulations of Labour Law.
Who are you?
It's none of your business.
He's my teacher.
I'm her husband.
I'm begging you.
Please give me another chance.
I must finish the task.
The last chance.
It's definitely my last chance.
OK
Thanks, sir.
I'm here.
Okay.
Go, go, go.
How about having some midnight snacks?
Not today.
I have to go home.
Why not finish our meals first?
It's OK. How about tomorrow?
Bye.
Bye. See you tomorrow.
I've changed the password.
What are you doing here?
I was off from work.
I drop by to check whether
you're still alive or not.
Come on. Are you ill?
Is there something wrong
between you and Yun Shu?
Yun Shu moved out.
Yun Shu ran away from you?
Watch your words.
She didn't "run away."
She just moved out.
What? Why?
I think we should keep some distance.
It's good for both of us.
Come on!
Did you do anything strange to her?
I just told her that we
should keep our distance
in front of other people.
It may be good for everyone.
She offered to move out
without my permission.
Yes.
So you get to keep your distance
from her like you wished.
Are you happy now?
How are you feeling now?
Not happy.
I
miss her.
Nian Nian, you're falling in love.
Nonsense.
Come on!
Yun Shu,
I just don't get it.
You are almost OK with everything.
But you're so stubborn
in the moving-out thing, why?
Because I think I don't want to
make do with my affection.
Mr Zhang doesn't love me,
so I can't stay at his home
and make trouble for him.
I also made trouble for myself.
Why are you staring at me?
You've changed.
You do seem kind of different.
All right,
forget those unhappy things.
I got my bonus.
How about having dinner together?
I have to go to work at the supermarket.
Have fun. I have to go.
Alright.
Bye
I'll hang out with you when I'm free.
Let's have dinner together.
No. I'll wait for Gu Xiao.
Gu Xiao?
You've met just once
within one minute.
And you have a crush on him.
Do you know him?
He may be a fraud,
a playboy,
or an outlaw.
Shut up.
I have made inquiries.
Gu Xiao is a nice man.
Perfect.
How?
After he graduated from our college,
he furthered his studies abroad.
He founded his own technology
company last year at home.
He's low-profile and gentle
with great ambition and lofty goals.
I don't buy the hearsay.
Seeing is believing.
Yi Yi.
Seeing is better than hearing.
Are you missing me?
OK!
OK
It's of course useful.
Yun Shu.
Yun Shu, we have to rehearse before we go
to visit grandpa in the future
otherwise grandpa may see the cracks.
Alright?
Got it, Mr Zhang
I'll tell you what I say to
grandpa through WeChat
in the future.
It's more than that.
If you have any trouble,
feel free to contact me at WeChat.
I'm always here.
Ok.
OK
Hello, Sir.
Do you want to get to know our beer?
They are our new arrivals.
Can you drink beer?
Not really.
But our beers
taste good.
Girl who can drink beer
has stories deep inside.
But I have no stories.
I'm not asking you
to tell your stories.
I'll pour you a sample. Have a try.
They are fresh
and they taste good.
The aroma of wheat makes me feel warm.
If you feel warm,
how about taking some
bottles of beer home?
I should drink warm beer
with a warm girl like you.
That's the drinking culture.
But I'm ill-educated.
Listen.
The drinking culture of China
originated from the Yangshao Culture
6,000 years ago.
Do you know that?
Yangshao...
The Law on the Protection of Women's
Rights and Interests
was revised in 2005.
It is clearly presented the
concept of sexual harassment.
Who are you?
Are you insane?
It's doesn't matter who I am?
The point is I know
according to Article 42, Paragraph 5
of the Law of PRC
on Public Security Administration.
Are you insane?
Yes. Watch out.
Thank you.
You can call the police
or ask for help
if you bump into this kind of situation.
I got it. Thank you very much.
Don't thank me.
Are you going to just take it
next time you run into such a situation?
I know people like him.
Most of the time, they
just want to harass you.
But if you ignore them, they'll walk away.
If you confront them head-on,
it'll affect your work.
After all,
those cans of beer should be to blame.
Sir,
thank you very much
I'm going to
work for the beer.
How about you looking around?
Director.
You're looking for me?
Yes, Yun Shu.
One customer ordered 20 boxes of beer.
Go with the delivery man later.
This is the address.
I...
The customer assigned you
20 boxes.
Just get out there
and you should meet your quota
for this month.
I think I've been to this place.
Really?
That's even better.
I'll let Wang of the logistics department
go with you.
Don't worry.
Thank you, director.
Yun Shu.
You made great progress recently.
Keep working hard.
Then I'm off now.
Okay.
Hello,
Hello, may I help you?
Hello, I'm from Huimin Supermarket.
I'm here to deliver
beer.
Yes.
Hold on. Let me make a phone call.
Okay.
Mr Meng. The one you
made appointments with is here.
OK
In the office at the corner.
Get in directly.
My beer is downstairs.
I'm here to deliver...
Never mind
I'll do it myself.
Just go in.
Okay.
Are you here for the interview?
I'm from Huimin Supermarket
to deliver beer for you.
Beer delivery?
Would you like to have a shot
at an interview with us?
Mr Meng.
You're the guy in the supermarket.
You're the company's...
Yes, want to have a try.
Hello, Yun Shu.
Hello, Mr Zhang.
Are you busy now?
Say it.
I have good news.
I got a new job
as an assistant at a law office.
I just passed the
interview this afternoon.
Congratulations!
Actually, I just want to tell you
that I'll be visiting grandpa
this afternoon.
I was afraid you might not know,
so I thought I'd notify you in advance.
Grandpa will be happy for you.
Come on.
Well, goodbye, Mr Zhang.
OK, bye.
You want to help her
but why do you hide it from her?
For Yun Shu,
me not helping her is the
greatest help.
I didn't expect that so many
years after graduation,
you'd come to see me
about your marriage contract.
You really trust me.
All the time, I trust your ability.
Yun Shu is so common.
She looks average
and not very smart.
Your type is special.
So in the future,
I hope you can help her at work.
Though we were competing for
the first place at school,
I always think we are in the same group.
So we can understand each other.
But after I saw Yun Shu,
I realized that maybe.
I never saw through you.
It doesn't matter.
Have you eaten yet?
Let me buy you a meal
as a thank-you.
OK.
I want to eat fried chicken.
The dining hall, then.
[Easter Egg Time]
Hello,
want to buy beer?
Mr Zhang,
why are you back?
Why are you taking them?
I want to help you sell beer.
Beer and diapers?
Why?
Come with me.
Walmart, the world's biggest retailer
once presented an interesting case.
That is, put beer and diapers together
and they are for sale together.
And sales volume showed that
the sales of beer were better
because it was with diapers.
Later, after their
analysis, they found that
many young dads
would shop at the
supermarket for their wives.
After they bought living goods
and diapers,
they would drop by to buy some beer.
Like this.
So according to the
analysis of statistics,
the proper adjustment
of goods distribution
can effectively change
the sales volume.
Awesome.
♫ You're a familiar stranger ♫