[Adapted from Wanzhi's
"Perfect and Casual"]
[Perfect and Casual]
[Episode 12]
Mr Zhang, are we almost there?
Yes.
Today.
Thank you for taking a
detour to send me back.
When will you go to
work in the new company?
The day after tomorrow.
Well.
By the way,
I have a gift for you.
Yun Shu.
Can you move back in?
Yi Yi.
Do you think I should
move back in or not?
You know the answer.
What is that?
In order to fulfil the contract,
I tried my best to control
my feelings for Mr Zhang.
I'm afraid...
I'm afraid I'll
fall in love with him if I move back in.
What to do then?
I don't know what you're struggling with.
The experience of predecessors
since ancient times tells us that
it's better to make friends
than make enemies.
So Mr Zhang and you
can't leave each other.
What an enmity.
Why an enmity again?
Don't you know
only enmity makes us live together.
You don't have to struggle.
It's impossible for Mr Zhang and you
to fall apart.
What if my mind is messed up again
when I see him next time?
Then you just
recite ancient poems, formulas and words.
What do you mean?
The year I took the postgraduate
entrance examination,
in order to lay off gaming,
I came up with a very good method.
When I want to play games,
I recite English words.
From A to C.
Finally, I laid off gaming
and I got a 90 in my English exam.
So?
So when you're unconsciously
attracted to Mr Zhang,
you can try memorising
things that you can't usually memorise.
That way, you'll be distracted.
What I usually can't memorise?
That means
statistics formulas and concepts.
That's it, you can memorise formulas.
Yi Yi, the day after tomorrow
is my birthday.
Can you come to my birthday party?
Gu Xiao.
It's Gu Xiao.
He invited me to his birthday party.
Text him back quickly.
I hope you can come.
OK, I'll be there on time.
Sis, look, it's our new house.
♫ Turning off the lights
in search of its trace ♫
♫ I walk steadily
on the path beneath my feet ♫
♫ I hear someone asking,
are you still here? ♫
♫ The kind person replies,
I've always been here ♫
I'm Party B, right?
Separate the daily life...
Mr Zhang,
It's yours.
♫ This love cuts through the crowd
in search of me ♫
♫ It isn't easy ♫
♫ I only wish to cherish it with you ♫
♫ Each and every moment ♫
♫ If I missed out, I will meet you again
in another lifetime ♫
♫ I recognise your eyes,
a secret that belongs to me ♫
Mr Zhang,
I thought you would be back tonight.
♫ The night will pass,
I am the dawn ♫
♫ Protecting this innocence,
evident in your eyes ♫
I'm back.
♫ I hear someone asking,
do dreams come to an end? ♫
The house looks different.
♫ I will keep you company in
the future, never letting go ♫
You like to sleep in,
so I got blackout curtains for you.
♫ This love cuts through the crowd
in search of me ♫
Their colour is the same
as that of your clothes.
♫ It doesn't make sense ♫
♫ All I can do is silently
feel your breath ♫
It's beautiful.
♫ And take you in my arms ♫
♫ If you care whether we'll still
be together in the next life ♫
You also changed the bed sheet.
The bed sheets and linens are new.
Do you like them?
♫ I want you to believe in my conviction ♫
The nightstand is also new.
♫ This love cuts through the crowd
in search of me ♫
You got no place to put your
underwear before.
♫ It isn't easy ♫
♫ I only wish to cherish it with you ♫
Thank you.
♫ Each and every moment ♫
♫ If I missed out, I will meet you again
in another lifetime ♫
Welcome home.
♫ I recognise your eyes,
a secret that belongs to me ♫
What are you doing?
Mr Zhang,
You're watching
stupid romantic drama?
By force.
Who dares to do that?
He calls me everyday
and lets me make
comments on his performance.
You said yes?
If I didn't say yes,
he would give me more calls
and force me to make more comments
on his performance.
So what do you think of his performance?
His performance
perfectly depicts a middle-aged man
with no dreams or goals.
And...
How should I put it?
Greasy.
It's a great word.
Accurate one.
Mr Zhang, you don't surf the Internet?
I usually go on math journal websites
to search for information.
Sometimes, I browse the
latest academic forums.
You don't
read news
or gossip?
I will read some substantive...
Gossip?
Why should I read them?
Because we want to
live a happy life.
I have math
so I'm living a happy life.
You like me, right?
No.
I've seen this episode.
I remember that Lu Yu once told me that
actors easily fall
in love with each other
when filming those scenes.
Do you think
we'll have such wrong senses?
Mr Zhang,
I think this kind of drama is
not fit for you.
So you shouldn't watch them.
Good night.
What's going on?
Why did you call me here so urgently?
Something is wrong.
What is it?
Gu Xiao has a birthday party today.
Why are you still here?
I thought
Gu Xiao and I would
celebrate his birthday alone.
But I found that
many beauties were around him.
Look at me! I'm so casual.
Gao Zhi Yi.
You're always confident
in your appearance.
Oh, save it.
Stop kidding me.
You want to outshine
all women at present
in front of Gu Xiao?
Yeah
I'm naive indeed.
Alright. You can do everything.
Come on.
Figure something out.
I'm too embarrassed to get in there.
Do I look good?
It cost me three months of salary.
Of course it's beautiful.
I'll repay you.
Go.
Gu Xiao.
We can also get this.
Yi Yi.
You're late.
I've been waiting for you.
Happy birthday!
Thank you.
Yi Yi.
You look so great.
Gu Xiao.
Who's this girl?
My girlfriend.
Gorgeous.
Come on.
Follow me later.
Come on. Cheers.
Stop showing off.
How sweet.
Come on. Come on.
Come on. Join us.
Happy birthday. Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Happy birthday.
Light the candle.
Thank you.
Happy birthday to you!
♫ Happy Birthday to you ♫
Happy birthday!
Come on. Thanks.
Thank you all.
Thank you all for coming.
Come on.
Thanks.
Thank you all.
Thanks for coming.
Drink up.
Mine is expensive.
Why don't you have it?
No. No.
Just hear me out.
Attention please.
Listen to me.
Let me introduce
a new colleague to you.
Yun Shu.
Hello, everyone, I'm Yun Shu.
Nice to meet you.
From today on,
Yun Shu's going to be my new assistant.
You can communicate with her directly
about work schedules and arrangements.
Yun Shu.
This is your seat.
Come to me if you have any questions.
Thank you.
Liane,
show her around.
Okay.
Come with me, Yun Shu.
I'll show you around.
Okay.
I'm leaving now.
Go.
OK
Back to work.
Lawyer Meng always works alone.
Why did he hire an assistant?
If you have a crush on a girl,
young and beautiful.
You will also hire her.
No.
I think
you're way more beautiful.
Get out!
Come in.
Lawyer Meng,
I'm really grateful
that you hired me.
Though I'm not a law major
and I can't help you
with professional problems,
I'll try my best to study it
and I'll try
to give
you professional help
in a timely manner.
What's going on? Why so serious?
You seem to go to the battlefield.
Take your time with your work.
You're my assistant
not my helper.
What's the matter?
Anything else?
Lawyer Meng,
I really want to learn.
I really want to help you.
You really want to learn?
OK, start with those three books.
Reference Book of National.
Judicial Examination of 2014.
What's the matter?
It's so many of them.
Alright. Lawyer Meng
I'll finish reading them.
Thank you.
They taste kind of spicy.
What are you looking at?
Yun Shu.
They're references given
by Lawyer Meng today.
Have dinner first.
I'm not hungry.
Lawyer Meng booked
fried chicken this afternoon.
I'm done.
Done?
I have some work to do.
You just place them here
when you finish your dinner.
I'll be back for them.
Hello, Wild Yu.
It's been a while!
How about having a drink tonight?
I'm busy. What's up?
Come on.
It's been a while since
you came to the bar last time.
And you didn't teach me
how to play that game.
Can you spare some time for it?
I'm busy.
I have to go.
Come on. Stay.
Come on.
Oh my god. For God's sake.
Just give me a break.
Nuts.
Listen to me.
I just...
Sickening.
Yun Shu.
Mr Zhang,
do you want to use pads?
Do you want to use the bathroom?
I'm here to tell you
I want to take a shower.
If you want to use the toilet,
then I'll be after you.
Never mind, Mr Zhang.
Thank you.
Okay.
Mr Zhang.
Go ahead.
Shut the door for me please.
Okay.
Why is she so hard-working now?
Yun Shu.
For me?
I want to drink milk just now.
So I warm one for you i passing.
Thanks, Mr Zhang.
You're welcome.
Anything else?
No.
Mr Zhang.
You're wearing the pyjamas I bought you.
Yeah.
Great.
It suits you well.
By the way,
can I help you with anything?
Well, these provisions are really hard
to understand.
I'm focusing hard
and reading word by word,
and I'm barely getting it.
So...
So?
So can you please turn that
TV down?
Otherwise I can't move on.
Of course.
By the way, Yun Shu.
You know I was a minor
in Law.
So I can help you
if you have any questions.
Don't bother.
Mr Meng said if I have
anything I can't understand,
I can circle them.
And he'll answer my
questions in the office.
Lawyer Meng.
The TV.
The TV?
Okay.
I'll fight for it!
Lawyer Meng.
What's Yun Nan's story?
She became the director
within such a short time.
Maybe she and Mr Liu...
It makes sense.
Her eyes betray
that she's not a restless one.
Her charming eyes
can really get men enchanted.
[The spring breeze]
Why are you here?
Oh my gosh. Is this Lu Yu?
Come on. How could it be?
It's Lu Yu.
Yun Nan knows Lu Yu.
She's really unusual.
Awesome.
She gets the leader's support at work
and flowers from an idol off work.
Hold on.
Thanks for your praise.
I have it all.
I have a good face
and good ability to get promoted.
Why are you here?
I'm here to take you home.
Who's your girlfriend?
You are.
When did I say yes?
I've slept at your house twice.
No.
Three times.
You're definitely my girlfriend.
I'd like to make it clear.
If you feel bored,
I'm free now.
So we can kill time together.
If you want to get closer to me,
then sorry.
I have no such plans.
Yun Lan.
Take the flowers.
Kill the time.
Sis.
Thank you.
You're on time today.
I visited grandpa today.
Is he OK?
He's OK.
I've been busy recently.
When grandpa feels better,
I'll go to visit him.
Sis,
I have good news for you.
What is it?
I got a new job.
What kind of job?
In a law firm.
Like you.
But I'm just an assistant.
I can't believe there is a company
willing to take you.
Sis.
Listen,
do Zhang Si Nian and you
take effective contraception?
Don't get pregnant.
No. We didn't do that.
What?
No.
You got me wrong.
Yes.
No, sis.
What are you thinking?
I didn't sleep with him.
That's good.
Listen,
you're in a contractual relationship.
You'll part one year later.
Maybe you can have a different story end.
But don't sleep with him
unless you
crazily love each other.
Got it?
Yes.
Sis.
Did you ever crazily love someone?
Not even when you were abroad?
I was busy with work every day.
So I never cared about that.
You had a hard time.
You look not smart.
But you did well.
You have to thank me.
I feel your thanks.
You're welcome.
But...
She is new here,
yet you assigned so many tasks for her.
You are exploiting a worker.
Exploiting a worker?
Zhang Si Nian.
When did you start to use
such an inappropriate word?
You know what I mean.
You let me
give Yun Shu a job.
You let me help her.
This is the beginning.
You overprotect her.
What should I do then?
I mean you shouldn't
influence our normal life.
You're in a contractual relationship.
It's not normal.
Yun Shu, you want to see Lawyer Meng?
Yeah.
I've finished all the
tasks he's given to me.
I'll take them to his office.
No way.
You'd better come up with a
reasonable cause to explain
why you are in my office.
Five, four, three.
Yun Shu.
This is the task you assigned to me.
I've reviewed the document.
Nice job.
Thank you.
Is there anything else I should do?
Nothing special.
Well, I'm off now.
Yun Shu.
You're the newcomer.
And I want to ask you
if you're under too much pressure
because of those tasks I assigned to you.
Of course not.
A slow sparrow should make an early start.
I'm starting from zero,
so I have to try harder.
Well,
will your life be influenced?
Of course not.
Actually, I don't have my own life.
Work is my life now.
Work is not only life.
Life shouldn't only be about work.
You have to learn to release your
work-related stress.
Lawyer Meng.
Sorry, maybe I'm a bit slow.
So I didn't fully understand your words.
But I'll try harder.
You're way smarter than someone.
At least,
you know what life is.
What's the matter?
It's okay.
I got a cramp.
Go.
Well, I'm off now.
Yun Shu.
What's the matter?
You...
You don't have to read your documents?
No.
Lawyer Meng gave me a day off.
He said happiness
matters most in our life.
Are you unhappy at the law firm?
I'm happy.
Since I went to work at the law office,
I feel that my life has
become more meaningful.
I'm really happy.
That's good.
Yun Shu.
Your work is tiring.
You don't have to
do those chores at home.
Why don't I get you a cleaning lady?
Don't bother. I can handle these.
Also, I can feel more relaxed
when I'm doing chores.
Doing chores makes
you happy?
Yeah.
It's my life.
Okay.
Mr Zhang,
what are some things
in your life
that makes you happy?
Math and work
I've told you that before.
I feel like...
Maybe you can try
doing something trivial.
Maybe they can make you feel far happier.
Alright. I'm going to
go to the supermarket.
Yun Shu.
Why not go together?
OK
What are you thinking about?
The supermarket offers discounts today.
I'm trying to figure how
I can buy those goods
at the lowest price.
Let me calculate.
10 percent off...
20 percent off...
Let me help you.
OK.
[Redeem points]
[Single-item discount]
[Spend 1000 yuan and get 299 yuan]
OK. I'm done.
Chap,
be honest.
Tell me
how I can buy them economically?
Right.
Just give us an example.
Am I right, girl?
You can buy goods worth 188 yuan.
And then
pay them
by using the coupon worth 25 yuan.
With 1000 points in your membership card,
you can get 10 yuan off.
Then you can get a red pocket worth 5 yuan
through WeChat Pay.
Then you can use these red pockets
when you shop next time.
It's the most economical way, I guess.
So.
Let's go.
Well,
you're similar to that lady.
Chap.
It's you.
Chap,
your way is really helpful.
Look.
We bought a bunch of stuff
and we got a lot of discounts.
You're a fine-looking
and economically rational person.
Chap, what do you do?
I...
He's a mathematics researcher.
Yes.
You must be a math
teacher in a middle school.
No wonder he's so brilliant.
Your girlfriend is beautiful
and able to keep house.
You're really lucky.
That's it.
She's not my girlfriend.
We're a married couple.
A married couple!
You're meant to be together.
Good for you.
It's our turn to pay. Come on.
OK.
Thanks, chap.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
♫ You're a familiar stranger ♫
Yun Shu.
♫ Who keeps appearing before me ♫
You're right.
What?
♫ You're clumsy yet kind ♫
♫ Ringing the bell in my heart ♫
Sometimes, trifles in our life can
indeed bring happiness to us.
♫ You predict and plan, but you can't
solve the problem called love ♫
♫ Let me tell you, just hold my hand ♫
♫ Looking up, I see
the most perfect you ♫