[Adapted from Wanzhi's
"Perfect and Casual"]
[Perfect and Casual]
[Episode 18]
Is this love now?
Do I ask too much?
Or
is Mr Zhang too reserved?
Will I be too unemotional?
Lu Yu also said
we can't deal with love
like we do business.
Yun Shu.
I was wondering
if we should add
a supplementary clause?
In the previous clauses,
the one.
"Falling in love with each
other shall not be allowed"
seems inappropriate for
our relationship now.
Then I'll revise it now.
Okay.
I was thinking,
since we are a couple,
and you like me
and I like you,
why don't we
cut all the
cumbersome procedures?
Do you agree?
How about
we sleep together tonight?
Mr Zhang.
I...
I'm sorry.
You...
What did
you say?
I said
since we are a couple,
it's okay for us
to sleep together,
right?
No problem.
You can bring "Wu Qian"
to sleep with us.
Then.
I...
I'll change the sheets.
How about.
Let's sleep.
Okay.
You...
What's your favourite position?
I mean
your sleeping position.
I prefer to sleep on my side.
Mr Zhang.
What position
do you prefer?
I also like to
sleep on my side.
Mr Zhang.
The quilt is gone!
Sorry.
How about.
Let's get closer.
So we can share the quilt.
Is this better?
Is it too superficial for us
to sleep like this?
How about
I'll sleep with you in my arms, okay?
Good night.
Mr Zhang.
I can't sleep
if you continue holding me like this.
Mr Zhang.
You're up early.
Did you sleep well last night?
Yes.
You...
You don't look so good.
Maybe I can only sleep well in my bed.
Mr Zhang.
Does the relationship
develop too fast?
How about.
Let's slow it down.
I'll look into it.
Okay.
Turns out
it was only a sleeping position.
We may as well sleep back to back.
At least I could get some sleep.
Miss Shen,
I’ve encountered a
difficult problem recently
and I want to ask you for advice.
Tell me.
What can possibly
be troubling you?
Simply,
someone you like
suddenly tells you
that you have a fast-going
relationship.
What does this mean?
Does it mean
we're not suitable for each other and
or
she wants to break up?
Most relationships
need
to develop step by step.
If any one step
were missing,
the relationship
would make the people involved
feel unsafe.
I'm still quite confused.
Then.
What on earth should I do?
For example, you should go to dinner
and watch movies
or date with each other.
You should spend
more time with each other.
Once you've spent some time together,
you'll know whether
you're suitable for each other.
I really ignored these aspects.
Yun Shu.
It's almost noon.
Just go for lunch.
You go first
I'll follow later.
Alright.
Then I won't wait for you.
Okay,
Lawyer Guan.
Come on, let's have lunch together.
You can draw
Mei.
Can I have a look?
I just
draw for fun.
Yun Shu,
do you keep a diary in comics?
My dad taught me this when I was a kid.
And I have the habit
when I grow up.
Nice.
You're as good as
many of our studio's
professional artists.
Mei.
Are you trying to poach her?
Lawyer Meng,
you reminded me.
Yun Shu,
are you interested
in becoming a professional artist?
It won't happen.
Yun Shu is our star.
All the more reason for me to poach her.
I'll have to think about
the terms under which
I'm willing to let Yun Shu go.
All right.
Please
stop making fun of me.
All right.
Don't joke.
Let's talk in the office.
Okay,
See me soon.
Well?
Last night,
was Zhang Si Nian angry
when you went back?
Not bad.
Looks like Mr Zhang
is finally enlightened.
Congratulations.
Lawyer Meng.
Thank you.
For what?
If you really want to thank me,
break up with him.
I'm kidding.
[Yun Shu]
[Mr Zhang]
Hello,
Mr Zhang.
Hello, Yun Shu.
Do you have spare time
after work?
Yes, I have.
I'll take you to a cinema tonight.
OK
Well
I'll pick you up
when you're off work.
OK
See you then.
Yes, yes.
Six, seven.
It's about to start.
How do you feel?
Did you sleep well?
Just now,
Mr Zhou
called me,
so...
Did you sleep well?
Is that satisfactory?
At what?
This morning,
you said that our love develops too fast.
So I asked Miss Shen for advice.
So.
So that's why you took
me to watch movies?
We got married before we started dating.
So I want
to make it up to you.
I'm
old-fashioned
and not interesting.
But one thing I am sure of is
I really like you.
So I hope
we can
get to know each other more.
I don't know
much about love.
But I can learn.
After all, I have quite
a learning ability.
And I'm willing to make some changes
for you.
♫ Turning off the lights
in search of its trace ♫
♫ I walk steadily
on the path beneath my feet ♫
Mr Zhang.
You've learned a lot already.
♫ I hear someone asking,
are you still here? ♫
Let's go.
♫ The kind person replies,
I've always been here ♫
Mr Zhang.
Can I sleep
in my own room tonight?
Of course.
The process of love,
I know it.
Then.
Good night.
Should I grasp it like this?
How is it going?
All right.
How about
I'll drive you to work
when you finish changing clothes?
No, thanks.
I can go to the company
again this afternoon.
All right.
Yun Shu.
Wait for me at home.
♫ You're a familiar stranger ♫
♫ Who keeps appearing before me ♫
♫ You're clumsy yet kind ♫
♫ Ringing the bell in my heart ♫
♫ You predict and plan, but you can't
solve the problem called love ♫
Come on.
I'm done.
♫ Let me tell you, just hold my hand ♫
Coming, coming.
Look at this.
It's started.
Okay,
Coming, coming.
I'm in a team fight.
Hold on.
I told you to stop
playing half an hour ago.
Then you pause it first.
-Wait for a while.
-For how long?
I’ve been waiting for
half an hour.
Soon.
Okay, okay.
I'll watch it with you.
[This game started with a pretty house.]
Lin Nuo.
Let me finish,
okay?
If I quit now,
my teammate will lose.
Do you know that?
Sorry, Yi Yi.
I shouldn't be angry with you.
You never yelled at me
when we used to be friends.
When we were friends,
you didn't stop me from playing games.
Then let's continue to be friends.
Okay, okay.
I know I was wrong.
It was agreed that
I should yield to you.
Don't make me use ultimate skill.
All right
I'm not angry anymore.
Let's watch movies.
Yun Shu.
You're still working
Mei.
Why are you here so early?
Is it just
four o'clock now?
I came to you specially in advance.
For what?
Here's our studio's recruitment notice.
There’ll be a centralized
interview in a week.
Would you like to try it?
[Hiring]
Recruitment season.
Comic master?
But I am an amateur.
Maybe I can't.
Think it over.
If you can earn money
through hobbies,
it's also a good choice.
Thank you, Mei.
[There were a few things I was game
for you never asked.]
[Like?]
[Eating ants.]
[Insulting the unemployed.]
[Loving you like crazy.]
What's wrong with you?
It's alright.
It's just so touching.
What's the matter?
No.
It's alright.
It's just so sudden.
I'm still immersed in
the plot of the movie.
I seem to have lost my contact lenses.
I'll get it.
Go and get it.
Yi Yi.
Can we talk?
Hi
sis.
Why is Mr Zhang...
We came here
to tell you something.
Yeah.
Cousin.
You found him?
Huo Qi.
Come in.
Yun Lan.
It's been a while!
Hi.
How dare you come to see us?
I thought I'd never see you anymore
in my life.
I'm here
to admit my mistake.
Mei.
Take a break.
I'll handle this.
Did you make Yun Lan angry?
How come?
I just think you're too tired
and want you to have a rest.
Yu.
You're so good at coaxing girls.
You brought Yun Shu
to the usury's office?
No.
I have to call the police.
Yun Lan.
I was wrong.
I really was wrong.
I promise
it won't
happen again.
I promise.
You really don't know how
dangerous it was that day.
If the brother-in-law
hadn't paid debt for me,
I really don't know
what Mr Tu would do to me.
Maybe...
I'm really scared
I'll never dare to do that again.
Yun Lan.
I can only pay back
the money I owe you little by little.
This is the repayment plan
guarantee I wrote.
I don't need it.
Men like you
never remember
unless you suffer a little.
Yun Lan, let me explain.
Can you give me another chance?
One last chance.
I've learned my lesson, seriously.
Besides...
Besides, my brother-in-law got me a job.
I can go to work soon.
I swear
from now on,
I will work honestly
and get my act together.
I'll make more money
to pay off my debts as soon as possible.
I'm not Yun Shu.
I don't believe
anything you said.
Don't be too harsh.
He admitted his mistakes.
You should let it go.
Can you change your
bad temper?
Do you understand what happened to us?
Do you know what he has done?
You don't know anything.
You're not qualified to
express your opinion here.
Although I don't know
about his wrongdoings,
I know your temper.
You always show no mercy
to others when you're in the right.
Since he has apologised
so sincerely,
can't you give him a chance?
This is my family's business,
not yours.
Get out.
Not my business?
I'm your boyfriend.
Your family business is also mine.
Brother-in-law.
Thank you.
Cousin,
I hope you can take care of yourself.
According to Yun Lan's temper,
she won't forgive you
for the second time.
Why don't you go?
Didn't you say you’d make money?
Why are you still here?
Thank you all.
Go back first.
I have work to do.
Hi.
All right.
Let's go back.
You go on with your work.
By the way,
Huo Qi just said
the house where Yun Shu lived before
will be rented out.
He has something there.
Help him with it.
No problem.
I want to go too
but
I have to work overtime this afternoon.
That's okay.
I can do that by myself.
Let's go.
Okay, sister, we're leaving.
Yun Lan, I...
Today's the day
my sister goes abroad to study.
From now on,
I'm all on my own.
Although I feel a little scared
and nervous,
but you can't.
That's okay.
Yun Shu,
you can do it.
Believe in yourself.
Fight on!
I have friends.
Our threesome was given
resounding nicknames.
Casual.
Love brain.
Copycat.
Although it's not very nice,
we don't care.
In a word,
they're basically okay.
Lin finally caught up with Yi Yi.
When I see them immersed in sweet love,
I feel happy and upset at the same time.
Where's
my love?
Everyone says college life isn't complete
without a romantic relationship.
I'm about to graduate.
Mr Right
please show up.
I hope I can find
an ideal job
and a generous boyfriend
after graduation.
Petty girl.
He can cook a good dish
and it's best for
him to have little talents.
He'll be gentle with me
and always amaze me with surprise.
Whenever I'm tired from work,
he’ll say to me,
"I can support you."
Sometimes he seems like a superman.
He'll show up in time
when I need him.
Twenty-four mate selection criteria.
If I look handsome,
I'm qualified up to 16 of the criteria.
Stop dreaming.
What a silly girl.
With your ordinary looks
and vague character,
nobody will like you.
I like you.
What can I do for you?
Just chit-chat.
I want to chat with you.
What do you think Yun Lan meant
by "we're of the different kind"?
She isn't human
or I'm not?
I think what she said
is reasonable.
Whose side are you on?
Who is your brother?
I'm on the side of logic.
I'm talking about Yun Lan here.
Why are you talking about logic?
Who is it?
You are a public figure.
You can always
encounter various things
in life.
You get used to dealing with the media
in daily life.
But for ordinary people,
they may never
encounter the same situation as you.
So she feels nervous
and more repulsive.
Really?
Are they all like that?
This is the normal behaviour logic
of ordinary human beings.
So
give Yun Lan more time.
Or
she’ll become more and more nervous
and repulsive to you.
Nian Nian,
I realised
you know a lot about women.
I just tried to
understand
the problems you just mentioned.
Gender attributes are not included.
That's why I can analyse it.
There seems to be a story.
What's wrong with you and Yun Shu?
I made a formal confession
to Yun Shu.
You finally did that to her.
Okay,
But the two of us
have just fallen in the relationship.
What do you mean?
I'm far worse
than Yun Shu's
ideal boyfriend.
Nian Nian,
I think you finally got it.
You're no longer a fool of love.
If you want to become
your girlfriend's ideal boyfriend,
I can give you some tips.
You?
With the way you and Yun Lan turned out,
What can you teach me?
That won't last for too long.
Okay,
Then tell me
how are you going to teach me?
Watch my show!
Many viewers treat my show
as a love bible.
Come on.
Are your shows legit?
Of course.
When you watch my shows,
do you get
a little
sense of love.
Not at all.
Are you a monster?
Many people get diabetes
because my show was so sweet.
Why don't you feel anything?
I didn't feel the sweetness
just a sickening feeling.
Okay.
You don't need to understand it anyway.
Let me show you.
Let me tell you something.
Trust me.
Girls like this very much.
They like to get pressed against a wall.
At that moment, girls will think,
wow,
you're so brave.
Get it?
I'll try it.
Let me tell you something.
Trust me.
Girls like this very much.
They like to get pressed against a wall.
Mr Zhang.
Are you all right?
You liar!
Look...
Did I hurt you?
No, no, no.
Why are you here?
You scared me.
I just came to see
if I can help you with something.
Here...
Look out!
Go on!
Handsome.
Mr Zhang.
Do you want to sleep together tonight?
Isn't this one of my
comic books?
Where did you find it?
I found it on that day when
I helped you move in.
How nostalgic.
It was so long ago.
I thought they were all lost.
Sorry, Yun Shu.
I saw one of the pages
without your permission.
It was about your
mate selection criteria.
I found out
I'm far below the standard.
I wrote this a long time ago.
I didn't understand
anything at that time.
So it doesn't count.
Mr Zhang.
You're already good enough.
But seeing your standards,
I suddenly realized that
I really don't seem to
know much about romance.
I've never given you surprises
or made you feel excited.
For me,
this can't be solved by mathematics.
♫ You're a familiar stranger ♫
It's alright as long as we
can feel the love of each other.
♫ Who keeps appearing before me ♫
So
♫ You're clumsy yet kind ♫
♫ Ringing the bell in my heart ♫
tonight,
do you want to sleep together or not?
♫ You predict and plan, but you can't
solve the problem called love ♫
♫ Let me tell you, just hold my hand ♫