[Adapted from Wanzhi's
"Perfect and Casual"]
[Perfect and Casual]
[Episode 13]
[Mr Zhang,
I have to work overtime tonight.]
[I'll return home late.]
[Okay.]
Professor Wu.
-Have you seen the news alert?
-No.
It says there will be a
massive drop in temperature tonight.
Really?
No wonder it's so cold.
I will go off work now.
Put on more clothes.
I'm off.
See you tomorrow.
Hey.
Please don't trouble me any more.
That's the warden's job.
You should cherish the chance.
In future, my dear Gu
will handle these things.
I really can't figure it out.
Why you girls
cover the flush with so much effort
then draw it on your face?
Well.
Pluck your eyebrows, then draw them.
Why?
You don't need to know it.
As long as my dear Gu knows it.
Dear Gu!
By the way.
That barrel water.
Change it for me, Ok?
Thanks.
Gao Zhiyi, I tell you
I will charge you if you
ask me to do it any more.
Be satisfied.
Next time?
You won't have another chance.
Such matters will all be done
by dear Gu
I mean, be careful tonight.
Gu Xiao doesn't look like
a gentleman.
You are just jealous of me
I am serious about it.
Do you still remember the day of birthday?
Girls who go there are really charming.
Nothing happens for no reason.
So, Gu Xiao cannot be a gentleman.
Are you
jealous?
I am just worried about you.
Shall I go with you tonight?
Nope! Urgh.
No one would take her ex to date
I am for your good!
If you feel happy.
You may lose your money and dignity!
I cherish my dignity, OK?
You!
Fine, Gao Zhiyi.
How dare you to do this to your ex!
I mean, If I am a little slower,
I would be disfigured.
Lawyer Meng.
What are you reading?
Nothing.
A comic book.
What's the matter?
Cartoons.
What's it about?
-He does not have any friends-
Is the author of this cartoon.
Jun Sakura.
He has been drawing this
for seven years.
Good for you, Yun Shu.
It's not so popular in China.
I never imagined that you are
also a fan like me
I don't care whether
he has friends or not.
But today, I have a new friend.
Me too
I finally have a friend
who also loves this cartoon.
I don't quite agree
I didn't say that.
He is so cold
and impersonal.
Maybe he's good in a cartoon.
But he's too mean in reality.
But in real life, I have
a friend just like him.
Me too!
Really?
Such a coincidence！.
Tell me.
How do you know
him?
Well.
That's a long story.
The subscriber you dialed is power off.
So.
Thanks to him
I didn't lose too much
because of my cousin.
Also because of him
I can make it so far.
And doing quite well.
Then what's the relationship
between you two？.
Relationship?
Friends, maybe.
Just friends?
Didn't you go further?
No
I think you have fallen in love
with him.
No！.
Don't you know
about his character.
How dare I!
[Zhang Si Nian]
Lawyer Meng.
How did you get to know Mr Zhang?
So, it's not a coincidence for
you to come to the supermarket.
It's Mr Zhang who told you.
It's Zhang Si Nian who
recommended you to me.
Then I went to the
supermarket and got to know you.
Finally you went to the law office.
But I want to tell you, Yun Shu.
After you had this job,
you really surprise me
with your performance and efforts.
For me, it's a huge surprise.
You have come up to this job
entirely with your own efforts.
We.
All want to help you.
So please don't mind about
how you get this job.
Don't worry.
No matter how I get this job,
I will do my best to complete it.
Hello, sir.
May I ask...
Sorry
I am looking for someone.
OK, excuse me.
Thanks.
Why are you drinking here?
Gao Zhiyi, please be mature.
Gu Xiao is not a
gentleman at all.
[Gu Xiao]
Hello.
Lin Nuo.
Why are you here?
Well.
I...
Why am I here?
Yiyi has drank too much.
It's too late now.
She cannot go back to her dormitory.
So I booked a room, and let her rest here.
I call you
to ask you to come
here and look after her.
After all, it isn't suitable
for me to be here.
Then, please take care of her
I gotta go.
Go to play basketball?
Yiyi.
Are you OK?
Lin Nuo.
What's the matter?
Come on, you are not drunk at all.
Of course I am not.
Don't you know about how much I can drink?
I have seen you downstairs.
Why are you here?
No
I am worried about you
I saw Gu Xiao making
you drink all the time.
I had a hard time
to find a pleasing boyfriend.
May you please stop
the surveillance on me?
It's not surveillance
I am
afraid that he doesn't
show respect to you.
Please
I am voluntary, OK?!
You have seen it.
He is a gentleman.
Why are you thinking him so bad?
No,
I am not!
I...
I mean.
Do you still like me?
Not at all!
Well.
You are my ex, not my dad
I am an adult now.
Even if I was cheated and tricked by him,
I am willing to.
Ok.
Whatever.
I didn't expect that we both like it.
So you have only read
it for a time.
And I got you?
Yeah.
Yun Shu.
Put my clothes on.
It's alright
I am not cold.
You will catch a cold.
No, thanks
I am not cold
I don't need it.
Why are you here?
Come here.
You came to pick me up？.
Yeah.
Mr Zhang is so considerate.
I have to keep my own things well.
Let's go home.
Hold on, Mr Zhang.
Tonight
I was going to have dinner
with Yun Shu.
Do you want to come together?
Really?
Yes.
OK
Just order what you like.
So delicious!
What do you want?
What's the smell?
Is it not so clean?
Shall we change a restaurant?
Smell?
Mr Zhang
I bet you haven't tasted Luosifen.
I am ordering.
A bowl of Luosifen with pig's intestines.
A quail egg.
Sour bamboo shoot, meat of snail
and Fried Toufu.
Good for you, Yun Shu.
Good taste.
You know Super Luosifen.
This is not the super one.
For it lacks.
Fried Beancurd Sticks.
Stop showing off.
Come on.
I want the same one with Yun Shu's.
Don't you order, Mr Zhang?
I can share with Yun Shu.
OK?
It's not sanitary to share a bowl.
Let's separate the food
I'll go to order.
She already knows it.
When you called me,
she was just aside.
She saw everything.
Then.
She said that she doesn't care
how she got this job
and that she will treasure it.
Zhang Si Nian.
You have a good taste.
Yun Shu is a good girl.
That's none of your business.
Yun Shu is my wife.
Contracted wife!
To be specific,
according to the contract,
you are at most
roommates.
What's your position?
What are you talking about?
Something happy?
Yes.
That's right.
Mr Zhang.
So, thank you.
Just deliver you clothes.
Never mind.
No
I mean the job.
Thanks for recommending me
this job
I just said it casually.
It's your own efforts to work
in the law office
I will try hard
and learn from Lawyer Meng
I will
live up to your expectation.
Mr Zhang.
Are you OK?
Aren't you having a cold?
Of course not
This kind of temperature
doesn't pose a threat to me.
Please come in.
Mr Zhang
I think you have a little cold.
No, I don't have a cold.
It's the best if you are fine
I have cooked ginger decoction for you.
It's good for both curing and prevention.
You can have a try
I'm OK.
Thank you.
And I doubt
it will prevent or
cure colds
deeply.
Such folk prescription
is not reliable
in terms of the evidence gathering
and resulting.
OK
If you don't want, I will take it away.
Wait.
Don't you refuse to drink?
I will prove it unreliable
myself.
Hot.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Let me cool it off.
Now better.
Is it?
Quite delicious?
Ok.
Let's go.
Yu.
What are you busy for these days?
You haven't been out
with us for a long time.
Tonight we have a party.
Full of beauties.
Will you hang out with us tonight?
No, thanks
I have something to do tonight.
What is more important than drinking?
Bingbing.
Do you have a dream?
Don't you think we should
practice out acting skills
for the future of China's movie industry?
Yu
I found that
I cannot keep up with you.
Please go on your practice
I will go drinking.
It's such a long way.
It seems only Yun Lan
can accompany with me.
I think our friendship comes to an end
tonight.
Then we should think about our love.
Knock it off!
There must be something wrong
with my opening.
What?
The TV drama that Zhao wants you to act
has forty episodes.
Forty?
That's too long.
Alright
I also think the law
topic isn't suitable for you.
Hold on.
Law?
Yeah.
You will act a lawyer.
Lawyer?
Law!
Mr Zhang.
If you are not feeling
well, just get more sleep.
Today I will go to work by metro.
The ginger decoction really works.
Yun Shu.
Lawyer Meng.
You came for me?
Liane
I'm going to sign you up for a class.
The company will pay for it.
OK
What is it about?
Economics or Criminal Law?
Emotion Management.
Emotion Management?
I mean, you are skilled
at divorce lawsuits.
There's no doubt on your professionalism.
Why did you show your
personal emotions
to the client?
It's Gao Mei's lawsuit.
How many lawsuits do we have with Gao Mei.
Don't you know?
For this time, Gao Mei has done too much.
It's her who should go to
learn emotion management.
There is only one person allowed.
Either you go
or you persuade her to go.
I see.
After this, don't make any fightback
I will make her satisfied.
Gao Mei will be here after a while.
Do I need to buy you an insurance?
No, thanks.
Are you my lawyer, or his?
He has an affair with other
woman, and transferred his property.
He wants me to afford half of his debts.
Why are you telling
me to make up with him?
Miss Gao.
Please calm.
Calm?
How can I be calm?
Why should I be calm?
How can you solve the
problem without being calm?
Mei.
I made this coffee for you myself.
Have a taste.
Liane.
What's going on?
Yun Shu.
Miss Gao
wants a divorce in three months.
But our evidence now
isn't enough to prove his
ex-husband transfer property.
So the plan provided is
propose an out-of-court settlement.
Do I have to pay so much to you
if I want an out-of-court settlement?
Did you make any deal
with the lawyers of my
ex-husband?
That's why you want me this?
Miss Gao.
You can question my ability.
But please don't
insult me on my professional ethics.
Mei.
Well.
Liane just made reasonable plans
according to the present evidence
to satisfy your needs as much as we can.
Well.
Don't worry.
If you are unsatisfied,
we can make further adjustments.
How can I calm down.
Every day, I am harassed by
banks and guarantee companies.
The account of my own company
faces the risk to be froze any time.
How can I calm down?
It nearly drives me mad!
What's the use of worrying?
It's all because of
your incompetence.
Mei.
Don't get angry.
Yun Shu.
Are you OK, Yun Shu?
Sorry!
I don't mean it.
Let's take her to the hospital.
No, I am fine.
In fact...
Mei.
As a lawyer, I suggest you.
No one can plan your life
as you wish.
As a man
I suggest you
there is no man in this world
loves women of bad temper.
If you have vigor.
Go to collect the evidence
of your husband's affairs.
Or you can accept our suggestion of
settle out of court as soon as possible.
Yun Shu.
Endure it
I will take you to hospital.
[Emergency]
I'm sorry. Sorry
I was so angry just now
I didn't expect it to be so bad.
Lawyer Meng.
Sorry.
It's not me who injured.
It's alright.
The doctor has said
it's just a scald.
It will be better after a few days.
Yun Shu.
Being kind is not advantages.
Lawyer Meng.
Mei doesn't really mean it.
This accident happened in the company
I have the obligation
to deal with it for you.
You have to believe me
I can deal with it myself.
Yun Shu.
Any compensation scheme
I will promise it.
I don't know what's going on
I cannot control myself at all.
All of a sudden.
You are just too over burden these days.
The divorce
really mess me up
I can neither do well in my company
nor get along with my child.
Maybe I am really
an unqualified woman.
Mei.
Don't say that
I don't think so.
We all prefer to deal with
problems with our emotions.
But if so, it will only be worse.
Sometimes, we need to change an approach.
The answer will come out itself.
Yun Shu.
So, thank you.
This is the most sincere
advise that I have heard for half a year.
May I ask who will
pay the bill?
The bill comes out
I will go.
Just have a rest.
Come here.
Follow me.
You just shouldn't
forgive her so easily.
People only grow in education.
I don't want to punish a mother
because of
these matters
I don't want to.
You impress me indeed.
Are you hungry?
You haven't eaten for such a long time
I will buy you something good to eat.
Thanks.
By the way.
You just said that
dealing with emotions
doesn't help it
at all.
That's sounds quite familiar.
It's said by Mr Zhang.
Why are you here?
How did Yun Shu injure?
Empyrosis
made by a client accidentally.
What did the doctor say?
Nothing serious.
Don't touch water.
Have a good rest.
Where were you then?
Just there.
Thanks so much.
Yun Shu.
Lawyer Meng.
Where is Mei?
She just left
Mr Zhang.
Does it hurt?
No, it's OK.
Doctor says it's not serious.
It will be better after a few days
I have told you before.
The company is complicated and dangerous.
Do be more careful.
Why are you so careless?
Complicated and dangerous?
This is a law office.
Not the wolf den.
Nothing dangerous, OK?!
Then please explain
why Yun Shu got bodily injury?
Mr Zhang, you are
using wrong words again.
Bodily injury
means damaging the
completeness of human body
or destroying the main
functions of human organs.
Yun Shu got a scald.
Then you think.
Yun Shu didn't get harm heavily enough?
Please don't mistake my meaning
I am just correcting your misuse of words.
Yun Shu.
Newly fried.
Have a taste.
Wait.
Oil fried food is not
good for the healing.
Yun Shu
I will take you home.
That's okay.
You haven't eaten for a day.
Have some.
Don't take it.
Let me feed you.
Did you wash your hands?
Of course yes.
You... I...
No...
Stop it! Both of you.
I will not eat.
Come on, Yun Shu.
OK. I will do it myself.
Thanks. Lawyer Meng.
Who is the relative of Yun Shu?
Take the wheelchair here.
I...
I am her boss.
I am her husband.
Yun Lan
I want to introduce a friend to you.
Lawyer Yun.
You seem quite different in saying hello.
So.
You know each other?
Be my assistant.
Mr Lu
is going to act in a law TV series.
We have the honor to cooperate with him.
What do you mean?
In the future three months,
he will experience the life here
being your assistant.
Why me?
Of course.
You are the trump card.
Trump card?!
Mr Liu, you know.
I have the cooperation with Xinda.
How can I spare time to train
newcomers?
See.
Don't shrink from difficulties
Mr Lu is so famous now.
This will achieve
better promotion effect.
Don't refuse.
Lawyer Yun
I would appreciate your advice.
Since you are a trainee,
I think
you should start from the very basic
send all papers of enterprise cooperation
in the two previous years
to my office.
So firstly,
I want to invite you
to my home to make a good teaching
of what's about law.
Please come in.
Lan.
This is the materials you need.
Put them there.
Thanks.
Lawyer Yun.
Please have some rest while working hard.
So much work.
When can you finish it?
Not mine.
Yours.
Don't you say you want to start from zero.
Read all cases in a weak
and make two conclusions of each case.
Handle them to me
on Monday.
Today is Friday, sis!
You have seven days a week.
Don't you have holiday in law office?
I don't know
I never have one.
Mr Lu, if you think this is too hard.
You cannot handle.
You can tell Director Liu
to change someone for you.
Lawyer Gao Nan over there.
She...
Don't...
I just love this kind of
busy and full life.
Monday is OK.
Read them out of the room.
Your schedule plan
has something to change.
When I arrive home,
I will send you after finishing.
And the Year Meeting...
Yun Shu.
Don't worry about your work any more.
Have a good rest at home.
Read more comics.
There are new updates.
I will read them the moment I arrive home.
You said you will work just now!
Well, Mr Meng
I have a request.
Go ahead.
Can you continue on.
Gao Mei's cases on your own?
She is living hard recently.
So
I will say yes to any your request.
Be careful of your hands.
Liane.
Make Yun Shu a full worker.
Add an accident injury insurance.
In addition.
Update companies' security system.
Add a camera in every meeting room.
Who is Gao Mei.
The client who scalded me.
So I guess I was right.
Did I do something wrong?
No.
You are yourself.
As long as you're happy.
By the way.
What's the name of uploaded comics?
-He does not have any friends-
The one said by Lawyer Meng?
You are finally awake.
What time is it?
Mr Lu, you slept like a log.
You slept like a log.
From 3:00 p.m.
to 9:30 p.m.
You didn't wake up one time.
For many times
I nearly tested your breath.
Where are you going?
Go home.
I will send you back.
Don't bother
I can go back myself.
What's your problem?
Blow hot and cold to me
Mr Lu.
Maybe you get the wrong feelings.
My feet has no feelings.
Scissors.
What are you laughing about?
I'm not laughing.
Maybe don't wash it.
After you take off the bandage.
If I don't have a shower for five days
Mr Zhang
will you throw me out?
It sounds reasonable.
But I think you shouldn't
have a shower tonight.
After all, your wound hasn't recovered.
It's alright.
I can do it.
Don't be worried.
Ok, I am taking a shower.
Go out
I will go for you after shower.
I didn't want an answer from you.
To be frank,
I do feel much better now
than before.
But even in this case.
I cannot cheat myself
or you anymore.
Yun Shu.
What's the matter?
I am fine.
Just slipped.
Is it serious?
It's OK
I can get up myself.
Be careful.
May I come in?
No.
Don't! Mr Zhang!
I am just wearing a batherobe.
Nothing inside.
♫ Turning off the lights
in search of its trace ♫
Can you get up?
Be careful.
♫ I walk steadily
on the path beneath my feet ♫
Yun Shu
I am in.
♫ I hear someone asking,
are you still here? ♫
Where are you?
♫ The kind person replies,
I've always been here ♫
♫ This love cuts through the crowd
in search of me ♫
♫ It isn't easy ♫
I...
Just in front of you.
♫ I only wish to cherish it with you ♫
Don't move
I am walking toward you.
♫ Each and every moment ♫
Grab on my hand.
♫ If I missed out, I will meet you again
in another lifetime ♫
♫ I recognise your eyes,
a secret that belongs to me ♫
Where is your wound?
Arm and leg.
Did it bleed?
No
I will take you out now.
Hold me on my neck.
Another hand.
Grab it tight.
Are you ready?
I am opening my eyes now
♫ The night will pass,
I am the dawn ♫
♫ Protecting this innocence,
evident in your eyes ♫
♫ I hear someone asking,
do dreams come to an end? ♫