[Adapted from Wanzhi's
"Perfect and Casual"]
[Perfect and Casual]
[Episode 8]
Now the groom
may kiss the bride.
Do you remember what I said?
Hands!
Be closer!
♫ You're a familiar stranger ♫
♫ Who keeps appearing before me ♫
♫ You're clumsy yet kind ♫
♫ Ringing the bell in my heart ♫
♫ You predict and plan, but you can't
solve the problem called love ♫
♫ Let me tell you, just hold my hand ♫
♫ Looking up, I see
the most perfect you ♫
♫ Close your eyes and feel me out,
the plain girl ♫
♫ Time is ticking, too much romance
is is left behind ♫
♫ You're here with me
as time passes us by ♫
Tell us was it for real or not just now?
What do you mean "real or not?"
The kiss!
It was fake.
Of course it was fake.
Really?
I think you kissed him for real.
I didn’t.
I swear. Absolutely not.
Nonsense!
The way you kissed
was clearly for real.
What way?
You just...
I just...
Like...
Like this...
Are you two for real or not?
Professor Zhang,
let's take a group photo
with your family, okay?
Okay.
Okay, I’ll get ready for that.
A moment please.
Ok.
Yun Shu,
Get ready. Let's take photos.
Coming.
Then I'll go there.
That...
You won't have feelings
for me again, will you?
Are you kidding me?
Our lips touched, that's all.
I just set an example.
Don't think too much.
What do you mean by "set an example"?
Come on, let's get closer.
Closer.
Okay, look over here.
Okay, everybody, smile.
One.
Two.
Three.
Okay, one more.
Smile naturally.
Look at the camera.
One.
Two.
Three.
Professor Zhang,
Let’s take a group photo.
Okay.
Grandpa,
Come on.
Come on. You two stand in the middle.
Everybody, come here.
Dr Zhang,
Come on
I'm sorry for being late.
There was an emergency.
You’re a distinguished guest.
Dr Zhang,
Thanks for coming over.
It's very nice of you to come.
Congratulations! Congratulations!
Thanks.
Get closer. Look at the camera.
Come on!
Can I stand with...
Grandpa, I'll stand with you.
Just a moment, everyone.
I'll change the SD card.
They look so happy.
I don't know when I will
have a fabulous wedding
with all the blessings.
Just focus on your graduate school.
I can tell your fortune.
You’ll be single all the
time within a decade.
You dare to curse me!
You must be Yun Shu's sister, right?
Hello, grandpa.
Both of you are so beautiful.
Yun Shu said that you are not married yet.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Why don't I introduce a nice man to you?
How about Si Nian's good friend, Lu Yu?
Grandpa,
I'm not right for him.
What are you looking at?
Just giving a sigh.
Life is full of surprises.
Why didn’t you cherish
me at the beginning?
Cherish, my foot!
Thank you for not marrying me
to help me avoid a tragedy perfectly.
I... I was so good to you.
You just regret it! You...
What do I regret?
I won't listen. I won't listen.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Come on, come on.
Get closer, everybody. Get closer.
Okay, look at the camera.
The bride, take the groom's hand.
Come on, be happy!
Can I?
Okay.
Come on. Look at the camera.
Is the love between the
bride and groom sweet?
Sweet!
How sweet is it?
Especially sweet!
Hold on.
This is a gift money for you.
Keep it.
Grandpa, I can't take this.
Take it. It's my wish.
Thank you, grandpa.
I need to thank you.
Today’s wedding celebration.
Perfect!
Especially the kiss just now,
that was even more perfect.
Academician Zhang.
You should get in the car.
It's time to go back to have a rest.
Okay.
Bye.
We'll see you in a few days.
Be careful.
Take care.
Mr Zhang,
This...
Here you are.
Grandpa gave this to you.
Just keep it.
I really can't take it.
I’ll change clothes.
Just wait for me.
Okay.
How about I take a shower first?
That’s good.
You... You go first.
[Turning off]
Yun Shu,
aren't you taking a shower?
I'm done bathing.
Then... Then I'll take a shower too.
Wait.
I'll go to your room
when you finish bathing.
My room?
Yeah.
We...
There’s still one thing left to do.
Okay.
Then I'll go first.
Is it very hot?
You sweat a lot.
I’m... I'm a little nervous.
Why are you nervous before we start?
Let's start.
Mr Zhang,
What on earth are you doing?
About
the kiss at the wedding today
I've thought about it for a long time.
I think I should reward you.
After all, I don't like
to owe others much.
Reward?
How are you going to reward me, Mr Zhang?
Just relax.
In this case,
you'll do better later.
It may take a little longer.
You lean it on your waist.
On... On the waist?
You’ll be more comfortable
when you do it later.
Let's start.
Mr Zhang,
I'm... I'm not ready yet.
You’ll never be ready if you don't do it.
I’ve already said it just now.
You’ll never know if
you’re ready for it unless you start
to do it.
I carefully selected this
elementary exercise for you.
Finish it in an hour and a half.
So I can figure out
the situation of your
professional courses.
Then make a tutorial plan for you
according to your situation.
I believe that
your grades will definitely be
among the best in the next year.
I thought...
What did you think of?
Nothing.
Pretty good.
OK.
Get ready.
Let’s start.
Mr Zhang,
I'm tired today.
We are tired.
You still have eighty-nine minutes.
Come on!
Childish!
Lady, you succeeded
in catching my attention.
Let’s call it a day.
Go to bed early.
Thank you, Mr Zhang.
Good night.
♫ Turning off the lights
in search of its trace ♫
♫ I walk steadily
on the path beneath my feet ♫
♫ I hear someone asking,
are you still here? ♫
♫ The kind person replies,
I've always been here ♫
♫ This love cuts through the crowd
in search of me ♫
♫ It isn't easy ♫
♫ I only wish to cherish it with you ♫
♫ Each and every moment ♫
♫ If I missed out, I will meet you again
in another lifetime ♫
I can't believe this is my wedding night.
♫ I recognise your eyes,
a secret that belongs to me ♫
I worked on the test paper all night!
Maybe God wants to tell me that.
I’ve changed from a graduate
to a man’s wife.
My life
has entered a new stage.
And maybe I’ll also face
some new life exam questions.
[Writing like crazy]
Mr Zhang, why don't you go first?
No, you first.
But it's not time yet.
And I didn't apply today.
There’s no need to strictly
follow the schedule in the future.
You go first.
Alright.
Thank you, Mr Zhang.
Why did he let me use
the bathroom first today?
Oh, that's right.
The ring!
The wedding ring!
I'm married to Mr Zhang.
I can't believe I forgot this.
Today's the first day after my wedding.
I'm married.
Please remember the password 2007.
Mr Zhang,
Why did you change the home password?
With my knowledge of your memory,
you shouldn't remember
these numbers wrong again.
Don't worry, I’ll keep it in mind.
It's our wedding date.
That's good.
Yun Shu,
Do you have any other plans today?
No!
Dress yourself up. We're going shopping.
Although it’s a contractual relationship,
Yun Shu doesn't delay
and becomes a love and career bumper.
Good!
What’s the matter? You're jealous.
I'm jealous? I'm not jealous.
Anyway, I'm almost there.
Almost there?
What do you mean?
Feng Qi and I!
It's basically settled.
Come on. Come on.
You two... In such a short term?
Of course it's true love.
I told him yesterday that
as long as he proposes to me,
I’d marry him.
Then what did he say?
Of course he said "okay".
Okay?
Just okay?
What do you mean "just okay?"
"Okay" means okay.
It means he agreed.
I'm thinking
if he’s planning
to propose to me now.
Not really.
A man who answered such a question
with merely "okay"...
No, it's not what you think.
Do you think everyone
is as incompetent as you?
Feng Qi is head over heels
for me.
See? He misses me all the time.
He sends messages to me all the time.
Do you want to hear it?
No, I’ll be "jealous".
Jealous? I’ll let you feel it really.
Yi Yi, I think our relationship
has developed too fast.
We'd better be friends.
Gao Zhi Yi, I told you that
you were being self-righteous
and being embarrassed.
You're overthinking.
Yi Yi.
Leave me alone.
Come on.
Yi Yi, don't be sad.
Feng Qi isn't good for you.
Mr Zhang,
What exactly do you
want me to do here today?
Although we are in a
contractual relationship,
you're still my wife
to outsiders.
So I hope when we go out
or when we visit
grandpa or our families,
you can present yourself
in a way that's more compatible with me.
A moment please.
Hello,
I want to ask if there's
a bookstore ahead.
Mr Zhang,
In fact, I appreciate your kindness.
You really don't have to
spend so much money for me.
It's my duty.
Let's go. It's just ahead.
Mr Zhang,
So you brought me here today
to buy books?
Then what do you think you want to buy?
Nothing. It's fine.
I've read the test paper
you finished yesterday.
You're found deficient in basic knowledge.
And tutoring needs to be
carried out systematically.
I made a book list for you.
Just find out all the books.
Statistics by editor-in-chief
Zhang Yi Hua.
Statistics.
I found it.
Applied Linear Analysis.
Theory of Probability
and Mathematical Statistics.
Statistics: From Statistics to Conclusion.
Found it.
Next.
Functions of Complex Variables.
Experimental Guidance
of Statistical Principles.
Management Statistics.
Found it.
Next tier.
From today on,
you should learn to read more efficiently.
Because this is just
your book list for a week.
One week?
By the way, there's another one.
High-order Statistics Method
of Independent Analysis of Components.
It's over there. I just saw it.
Where is the book, Mr Zhang?
I see it.
Thank you, Mr Zhang.
Are you hungry?
Not me.
There's no one else here.
Really not me!
Let's eat something.
Good afternoon! What
would you like to order?
Are you dissatisfied with the food here?
No! No!
Then you want to eat something else?
I... I want fried chicken.
Sorry, we don't offer fried chicken.
OK, then I'll order something else.
Is there any fresh chicken in the shop?
Yeah.
Do you have linseed oil or olive oil?
You have eggs, flour and bread crumbs
and all kinds of spices, right?
You have all the things I said.
Then there should be no
difficulty in making a fried chicken.
The oil temperature should
be kept at 180 degrees.
The error should not exceed three degrees.
Only then will it have a nice texture.
I'm sorry, sir. Restaurant policy.
We can only cook what's on the menu.
Mr Zhang,
I remember you.
You’re from Zheng Ben University, right?
In Mr Zhang's class last time,
you sat in front of me.
Sister, you do have a good memory.
I major in Economics.
This is my senior year.
I often go to Mr Zhang's class secretly.
I'll deal with it.
You go on with other things.
Mr Zhang,
What would you like to eat today?
A seafood salad with vinegar dressing
and a fried chicken
with canola oil.
Fried chicken?
Who told you to add
dishes without permission?
The rhythm of the kitchen
is all messed up by you.
The dishes they requested
weren't complicated.
So I...
Can you do that as long as
it's not complicated to make?
I just...
Sorry, manager.
Please don't say that about her.
We made her do it.
So please stop blaming her.
Guest.
We have met all your requirements.
Please stop interfering with
my discipline of my employees.
Then you can't personally attack her.
Because she's useless
and ruins business.
On what background can you say that?
If all of your employees were like her,
your restaurant would be better off.
What makes you say that?
Because the other
employees in your restaurant
look unhappy.
She's the only one
who deals with the guests with a smile.
Smile can make more profits?
Why are you all so naive?
You.
This is really not naive.
I'm sure you don't know
the variable relationship between the
index model of customer satisfaction
and beverage profits.
The catering industry
belongs to the service industry.
Customer satisfaction
is the primary productivity.
Instead of blindly rejecting
the guest's request,
it's better to adapt to
meet the needs of guests.
I suggest you study
index models carefully.
If you can't understand,
you can ask her for advice directly.
And she'll give you all the answers.
Come on.
Besides,
have you noticed
the man by the window?
He's a Michelin star inspector.
Don't you want your restaurant
to be on the Michelin Restaurant Guide?
Mr Zhang, I have a question for you.
How did you know the
one by the window just now
was a Michelin star inspector?
I really didn't know.
Then you lied?
A white lie is not a lie.
That's what you said.
Mr Zhang, don't worry
I'll definitely finish reading
these books when I go back.
And
I certainly won't let you down.
I'll do my best in my senior year
to graduate.
What about after that?
Mr Zhang,
Do you also feel that
I'm a useless person?
Why do you think about yourself like that?
Does it matter what I think?
Anyway, everyone
thinks I'm fooling around.
At least in my opinion,
you aren't nothing
or a useless person either.
You just haven't found
your place yet.
Just like the theory of
"casual" you told me about.
You want to make
yourself at ease and happy.
This is indeed a choice
and a good idea.
But the reality
usually makes you feel
that it's counterproductive.
Oh?
Do not worry.
This year,
I'll try my best to help you.
Let's start with a degree certificate.
I believe that when the contract ends,
you're sure to find
your own life direction.
Let's go home.
Okay.
Yi Yi.
I just thought about it.
In fact, I think Zhang Si Nian
is a very nice person.
Think about it.
He is thoughtful, straightforward,
handsome, rich,
with high IQ and EQ,
and quite responsible.
I see.
You know what?
I know what's wrong with you.
What's wrong with me?
Yun Shu,
You like Zhang Si Nian.
Nonsense.
How can I like Zhang Si Nian?
Question.
Answer.
Coffee or tea?
Coffee.
Latte or American coffee?
Latte.
Cold or hot?
Cold.
Red or blue?
Red.
Summer or winter?
Summer.
Chinese or Math?
Chinese.
Wu Yi Fan or Zhang Si Nian?
Zhang Si Nian.
Yun Shu.
Mr Zhang, when did you come back?
It's been more than three
minutes since I came back.
Did you just
wipe your face with my clothes?
No, I was just checking
if the clothes are clean.
It turned out that it didn't
seem to be very clean.
So I'm going to wash it again.
Wait.
I have something
to talk to you about.
I'll take a shower first.
Mr Zhang,
Yun Shu,
Sit over here.
I bought you a financial product
with the gift money grandpa gave you.
And a supplementary agreement
was added to the contract.
Income from wealth management products
will be your monthly expenses.
If there's no problem,
just sign here.